<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2019-2020s on Bloomington Playwrights Project</title>
    <link>http://newplays.org/event/2019-2020/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2019-2020s on Bloomington Playwrights Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 18:30:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://newplays.org/event/2019-2020/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>BPP&#39;s 41st Birthday Celebration</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2019-2020/bpps-birthday-bash/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 18:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2019-2020/bpps-birthday-bash/</guid>
      <description>After how much fun we had last year, BPP is throwing itself another Birthday Celebration in 2020! Start the night out at 6:30 with donated food, wine, and beer! Then move into the theatre for the announcement of our 2020-2021 Season and a staged reading of the 2011 SMASH HIT Still the River Runs starring the original cast (Gabe Gloden &amp;amp; Daniel J. Petrie). Then stick around for the announcement of the 2020-21 Season (our 41st!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ike &amp; Julie Arnove PlayOffs</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2019-2020/ike-and-julie-arnove-playoffs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2019-2020/ike-and-julie-arnove-playoffs/</guid>
      <description>Batter up for the Ike &amp;amp; Julie Arnove PlayOffs! It&amp;rsquo;s almost that time of year again when we separate the contenders from the pretenders, the pros from the joes, the heroes from the zeros. Yes, that’s right - the baseball playoffs are just around the corner. In celebration, the BPP is presenting its most electrifying, action-packed, and anticipated fundraising event of the year, the Ike &amp;amp; Julie Arnove PlayOffs!
Just what are The PlayOffs, you ask?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simon Coronel&#39;s Magic Smackdown</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2019-2020/simon-coronels-magic-smackdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2019 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2019-2020/simon-coronels-magic-smackdown/</guid>
      <description>Simon Coronel’s Magic Smackdown combines the amazing magic of Penn &amp;amp; Teller’s Fool Us, the humor and fun of Whose Line Is It Anyway, and the excitement of live voting you find on American Idol. This wholly original evening of entertainment stars award-winning stage and television magicians (and regulars of the Magic Castle) competing for both your attention and your affection. It’s an exhilarating and interactive magic show that will keep you laughing and amazed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mind Tricks with Max Major</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2019-2020/mind-tricks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2019-2020/mind-tricks/</guid>
      <description>World-renowned mentalist, Max Major, has given over 2,000 live performances and 100 television appearances. But after he baffled our minds at BPP in 2017 with his latest show, Max took a sudden and unexpected break from performing to focus on his most difficult trick yet: recovering from Lyme disease. Two years later, he’s traveling back to BPP to make his triumphant return to the stage and picking up where he left off, with a new outlook on life and incredible new feats of mind-reading and magic.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>