<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2016-2017 on Bloomington Playwrights Project</title>
    <link>http://newplays.org/series/2016-2017/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2016-2017 on Bloomington Playwrights Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 18:30:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://newplays.org/series/2016-2017/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Vintage Songs</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2016-2017/vintage-songs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 18:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2016-2017/vintage-songs/</guid>
      <description>This June, we invite you to expand your dramatic palate with an all-new show featuring a performance of favorite songs from BPP&amp;rsquo;s original musicals, as well as the announcement of the 2018-19 Season. The evening begins Thursday, June 14, 2018 with a full buffet dinner at 6:30pm, followed by the performances at 7:30pm. A cash bar with wine will also be open. This year we’ll be at the Oliver Winery Creekbend Vineyard at 7508 N Woodall Road, in Ellettsville.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happily After Ever</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/happily-after-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/happily-after-ever/</guid>
      <description>Newlyweds Darren and Janet want nothing more than to build the perfect life together. But when Janet gives birth to a baby with both male and female genitalia, they find themselves in the unlikely position of having to choose a gender for their child - all while competing with the perfect couple next door and dealing with a misunderstood family dog - in this hilarious battle of the sexes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miniplay Playwriting Competition</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2016-2017/miniplay-playwriting-competition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2017 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2016-2017/miniplay-playwriting-competition/</guid>
      <description>2016 Winners  Jack Nelson, Grade 6, University Elementary School Hunter S.W. Broomall, Grade 4, University Elementary School Jack Knudsen, Grade 3, Unionville Elementary School Wilson Lommel, Grade 4, Unionville Elementary School Dahlia Ritter, Grade 6, Childs Elementary School Sandro Smith, Grade 6, University Elementary School  2017 Event The winning plays will be performed by local actors on Sunday, April 9th! Admittance will be granted with a first-come first-serve basis with limited seating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calling All Kates</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/calling-all-kates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2017 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/calling-all-kates/</guid>
      <description>Marc gets dumped by his fiancé, Kate McBride, right before their wedding and honeymoon around the world. He’s now single and left to travel the globe alone since his plane tickets are non-transferrable and non-refundable. In an act of desperation, Marc posts an ad online for the only companion who could legally join him&amp;hellip; someone with the exact same name as his ex-fiancé. Set loose in a bunch of different foreign countries, strangers Marc and Kate must get to know one another and learn to get along in the wake of Marc&amp;rsquo;s heartbreak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Escape the Room</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2016-2017/escape-the-room/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2017 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2016-2017/escape-the-room/</guid>
      <description>You are a member of the IU Basketball team and you’ve been locked in Tom Crean’s office by the evil Boilermakers. If you don’t find a way to get out, IU will have to forfeit and Purdue will win the big game. The stakes are high – but will you escape in time?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Row After Row</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/row-after-row/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/row-after-row/</guid>
      <description>Historical accuracy is paramount to Cal and Tom, two hardcore Civil War re-enactors, fresh off their latest Gettysburg battle. But their accuracy is compromised when they’re joined by a soldier with a less than authentic confederate uniform&amp;hellip; and the wrong gender. Straddling 1863 and today, ROW AFTER ROW is a dark comedy about choosing your cause and finding your courage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/home/</guid>
      <description>Katherine escaped from her small Texas home and her hypochondriac mother 9 years ago. When she finally steps back into her childhood home, Katherine is immediately overwhelmed by the familiar. Every room seems to have a story. Every corner of the house holds another recollection. Katherine’s memories become so vivid, in fact, they appear to come alive before her eyes. Both humorous and heartbreaking, HOME explores parenting and childhood with unflinching honesty, questioning what it means to grow older, and whether we truly have the capacity to grow up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ike &amp; Julie Arnove Playoffs</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2016-2017/ike-and-julie-arnove-playoffs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2016-2017/ike-and-julie-arnove-playoffs/</guid>
      <description>Donate to the 2016 Ike &amp;amp; Julie Arnove PlayOffs!
It’s that time of the year again for the Ike &amp;amp; Julie Arnove PlayOffs. The time of year when we separate the contenders from the pretenders, the pros from the joes, the heroes from the zeros. Yes, that’s right, the baseball playoffs are just around the corner. In celebration, the BPP is presenting its most electrifying, action-packed, and anticipated fundraising event of the year, the Ike &amp;amp; Julie Arnove PlayOffs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Day Mourning Period</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/30-day-mourning-period/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/30-day-mourning-period/</guid>
      <description>Larry, Susan and Craig are locked in mind-numbing sales jobs that are slowly draining each of them. But everything changes when their boss, Mr. Clybourne, kills himself one morning, and their company grants the office a 30-day &amp;ldquo;mourning period&amp;rdquo; with no sales goals, no dress codes and no corporate oversight. With a newfound freedom and an unbridled sense of adventure, the three thrust themselves into their own tale of rebellion, and over the course of their mourning period they build a castle out of office supplies, encounter an army of rats, fight with water balloons, drink excessive amounts of tequila, discover meaning in their previously meaningless monotony and ultimately attempt to right the wrongs of their company’s impersonal policies in their own makeshift revolution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annual Gala</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2016-2017/annual-gala/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2016 18:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2016-2017/annual-gala/</guid>
      <description>The BPP Annual Gala will be a lively, classy evening! Cocktail hour will take place in three different areas from 6:30-7:30. And the dry ice cocktails are back by popular demand! You&amp;rsquo;ll be able to mingle, bid on silent auction items, and check out the delicious appetizers and beverages! The main event takes place in the auditorium from 7:30 - 10:00 and will feature entertainment by magician Caleb Wiles, as well as the live auction and an amazing dinner from IMU Catering.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>