<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reva Shiner Comedy Award Winner on Bloomington Playwrights Project</title>
    <link>http://newplays.org/awards/reva-shiner-comedy-award-winner/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Reva Shiner Comedy Award Winner on Bloomington Playwrights Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 19:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://newplays.org/awards/reva-shiner-comedy-award-winner/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Beating A Dead Horse</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/beating-a-dead-horse/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/beating-a-dead-horse/</guid>
      <description>Brothers Steve and Marty Martin are on the brink of closing their failing pet funeral home, until an eccentric (and rich) new customer comes in with an amazing proposition: plan a funeral for her nearly dead racehorse, and she’ll give the boys a fortune to keep their business afloat. The only problem? The horse won’t die. With everything on the line, the two embark on a hysterical journey to see how far they’ll go to make their dreams come true, in this laugh-a-minute screwball comedy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Day Mourning Period</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/30-day-mourning-period/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/30-day-mourning-period/</guid>
      <description>Larry, Susan and Craig are locked in mind-numbing sales jobs that are slowly draining each of them. But everything changes when their boss, Mr. Clybourne, kills himself one morning, and their company grants the office a 30-day &amp;ldquo;mourning period&amp;rdquo; with no sales goals, no dress codes and no corporate oversight. With a newfound freedom and an unbridled sense of adventure, the three thrust themselves into their own tale of rebellion, and over the course of their mourning period they build a castle out of office supplies, encounter an army of rats, fight with water balloons, drink excessive amounts of tequila, discover meaning in their previously meaningless monotony and ultimately attempt to right the wrongs of their company’s impersonal policies in their own makeshift revolution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kalamazoo</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/kalamazoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2014 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/kalamazoo/</guid>
      <description>When Peg, a 70-something, Irish Catholic bird lover meets Irving, a 70-something Jewish, metal detector-toting East Coaster on an online dating site, it feels like love at first click. But after their crazy margarita-filled first date, complete with body shots and morning-after tattoos, Peg and Irving find that they still have a little aging to do if they want to forget their past and move forward into a future together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mad Gravity</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/mad-gravity/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2014 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/mad-gravity/</guid>
      <description>Archie and Eudora have built a live studio audience in their living room. Being constantly observed helps them to lead an honest and honorable life. But things get awkward when some important visitors get a massive case of stage fright. Then, when it&amp;rsquo;s announced that an asteroid may be heading cataclysmically towards the Earth, all social order breaks down and the honest and honorable life takes a backseat to a frenzied, panicked mayhem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ampersand</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2012-2013/ampersand/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2013 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2012-2013/ampersand/</guid>
      <description>Things aren&amp;rsquo;t working out for Kate and Marlowe. He&amp;rsquo;s an unemployed whiner, and despite her best efforts to stick with him, Kate just couldn&amp;rsquo;t help cloning him. Twice. When one of the clones slips into Marlowe&amp;rsquo;s life, and Kate discovers that she might not actually be the original Kate, things get scarier and funnier at the same time. Just what is marriage? And how far will we go to change each other—and ourselves—to stay together?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>