<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>30 Days of Dinner on Bloomington Playwrights Project</title>
    <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 30 Days of Dinner on Bloomington Playwrights Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 18:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Days of Dinner</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/spier_ellenwood/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/spier_ellenwood/</guid>
      <description>Date: January 31st Time: 6PM Location: 2110 E Covenanter Dr., Bloomington IN 47401 Theme: Venetian Masquerade Mystery Party Food: There will be 5 courses to the meal including drinks. Attire: Cocktail - Please wear something black, green and/or blue Mask: Required - There will be a prize for the best mask Childcare: Babysitting at the event can be provided for an additional $15. Children will be downstairs the whole party with the sitter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Days of Dinner</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/butler/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/butler/</guid>
      <description>Date: January 26th Time: 6PM Location: 4249 S Clear View Dr, Bloomington IN 47403 Theme: Melting Pot Party Food: Wide assortment of foods cooked around a communal melting pot. Host open to dietary restrictions (contact Brad Schiesser below if you have dietary restrictions) available with Wine provided by Oliver Winery  Longtime friend, subscriber, Playoff Director, and supporter of BPP, Sheila Butler and Prince Butler will be hosting a dinner party at their home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Days of Dinner</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/johnson_solberg/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/johnson_solberg/</guid>
      <description>Date: January 25th Time: 6PM Location: 344 S Rogers St, Bloomington IN 47403 Theme: Scandinavian delights Food: A sit down dinner of Scandinavian cuisine, from the Scandinavian Hostess with the Mostest Sonja Johnson  Long time donors, volunteers, and BPP Angels Sonja Johnson and Keith Solberg are opening up their home for yet another fantastic mini-party! Their get togethers are BPP lore and we don&amp;rsquo;t want you to miss out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Days of Dinner</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/michaelsens/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/michaelsens/</guid>
      <description>Date: January 25th Time: 5:30 PM (Will begin promptly to allow for actors and attendees to be at the performance that evening) Location: 2605 E Seminary Dr., Bloomington IN 47401 Theme: Cocktail Party Food: Cocktails and heavy hor d’ouvres at their fabulous home. If you have dietary restrictions please contact Brad Schiesser below.  Director for our upcoming production of APROPOS OF NOTHING Jonathan Michaelsen and his wife Miah, the Deputy Director of the Indiana Arts Commission, are opening up their amazing home to guests wanting to support BPP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Days of Dinner</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/spier_arnove/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/spier_arnove/</guid>
      <description>Date: January 25th Time: Sunset Location: 2110 E Covenanter Dr., Bloomington IN 47401 Theme: Special Shabbat Dinner Food: Traditional Friday Sabbath meal with wine Childcare: Babysitting at the event can be provided for an additional $15. Children will be downstairs the whole party with the sitter.  Board members Ellee Spier and Bob Arnove invite you to a very special Shabbat Dinner in support of the BPP. The event will be at Ellee&amp;rsquo;s home on Covenanter Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Days of Dinner</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/welch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/welch/</guid>
      <description>Date: January 24th Time: 5:30-7:30PM Location: 1211 S. Walnut St, Bloomington IN 47401 Theme: Mead Tasting! Food: &amp;ldquo;Catered in food as well as mead tastings from Oddball Fermentables&amp;rdquo; Some food will be Vegetarian. If you have other dietary restrictions please contact Brad Schiesser below.  BPP Board member Von Welch and Oddball Fermentables are teaming up to bring you this special opportunity to support BPP and enjoy the local crafted mead from right here in Bloomington.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Days of Dinner</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/susan_jones/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/susan_jones/</guid>
      <description>Date: January 22nd Time: 6PM Location: 3508 E William Ct., Bloomington IN 47401 Theme: Moroccan themed dinner Party Food: Moroccan main course with Vegetarian option.  Long time BPP Supporters/Directors Circle Members/Guardian Angels Susan and David Jones are having a fantastic Dinner party at their lovely home on the South side. Moroccan food will be served and a fun BPP game will accompany the meal. This is going to be a fantastic affair you won&amp;rsquo;t want to miss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Days of Dinner</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/daily/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/daily/</guid>
      <description>Date: January 20th Time: 6PM Location: 3512 S Tudor Ln., Bloomington IN 47401 Theme: FAMILY NIGHT Food: &amp;ldquo;Whatever the kids decide to make that night&amp;rdquo;  BPP Board member and Artistic Director of the John Waldron Arts Center Paul Daily will be opening up his home so the whole family can be a part of this experience. Not only will Paul&amp;rsquo;s lovely wife Courtney be there but also their 3 children who will be acting as chefs and servers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Days of Dinner</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/sideli/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/sideli/</guid>
      <description>Date: January 26th Time: 6PM Location: 1410 E University, Bloomington IN 47401 Theme: Dinner Party Food: A fantastic sit down dinner. Wine provided by Oliver Winery  Longtime BPP supporter Kathy Sideli will be having a dinner party at her home
THIS DINNER IS SOLD OUT
Price: $50</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Days of Dinner</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/shakalis_bright/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/shakalis_bright/</guid>
      <description>Date: January 17th Time: 6:30PM Location: 3207 E Kristen Ct., Bloomington IN 47401 Theme: &amp;ldquo;Sparkling Midwinter Spontaneity.” E.g., “Please bring to show — or wear — something sparkly that evokes memories for you. (Or, not.)&amp;rdquo; Food: &amp;ldquo;chicken dish, hor d’ouvres, dessert, bread, beer, wine, salad, etc.&amp;rdquo; If you have dietary restrictions please contact Brad Schiesser below.  Herald Times Arts Reviewer Connie Shakalis (Vicky Richards in TUNING IN) and Long time BPP Supporter, Directors Circle Members, and play reader Anne Bright, invite you to a dinner party that will put some shine into the dreary month of January.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Days of Dinner</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/martin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/martin/</guid>
      <description>Date: January 17th Time: 6PM Location: 2368 Winding Brook Circle, Bloomington IN 47401 Theme: Dinner Party Food: &amp;ldquo;Indian Cuisine&amp;rdquo; with Vegetarian options available. If you have other dietary restrictions please contact Brad Schiesser below.  BPP Board member David Martin will be hosting a dinner of Indian cuisine. David a talented cook himeself will make a fantastic meal that will transport you to the subcontinent. You don&amp;rsquo;t want to miss this one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Days of Dinner</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/shakespeare/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/shakespeare/</guid>
      <description>Date: January 16th Time: 5:30-7 Location: 1806 E Thornton Dr., Bloomington IN 47401 Theme: Wine Tasting Food: &amp;ldquo;Appetizers paired with several incredible wines from around the world&amp;rdquo;  BPP board member Rob Shakespeare and his wife (longtime BPP supporter) Marie will be hosting a Pinot Noir Wine Tasting with selections from famous regions. The tasting will be paired with delicious appetizers at their home.
THIS DINNER IS SOLD OUT</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Days of Dinner</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/engber/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/engber/</guid>
      <description>Date: January 13th Time: 6PM Location: 2731 S Silver Creek Dr., Bloomington IN 47401 Theme: Tapas From Around the World Food: Tapas from Around the World including Spain, Greece, and Japan. Some Tapas will be Vegetarian. If you have other dietary restrictions please contact Brad Schiesser below  BPP Board member Michael Engber and his wife Cheryl (both longtime supporters) will be hosting a culinary delight at their home with a series of small plates or Tapas from around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Days of Dinner</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/ted_jones/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/ted_jones/</guid>
      <description>Date: January 13th Time: 4:30PM Location: 1607 S Woodruff Ln., Bloomington IN 47401 Theme: Curated Wine Tasting Food: &amp;ldquo;Heavy hors D&amp;rsquo;oeuvres, some of which will be Vegetarian, and a selection of wines to taste.  This one is not to be missed! Ted Jones (The one whose name is on the side of the BPP Building) is hosting a curated wine tasting with passed hors D&amp;rsquo;oeuvres at his fabulous home in Bloomington.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Days of Dinner</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/freund/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/freund/</guid>
      <description>Date: January 12th Time: 6PM Location: 2100 S. Olcott Blvd., Bloomington IN 47401 Theme: &amp;ldquo;Theatre Charades&amp;rdquo; Food: A sumptuous dinner with Wine provided by Oliver Winery  BPP Board President Sandra Freund and her husband Don will be hosting theatre charades and a fantastic sit down dinner.
THIS DINNER IS SOLD OUT
Price: $50</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Days of Dinner</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/stavropoulos_molenda/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/stavropoulos_molenda/</guid>
      <description>Date: January 11th Time: 6PM Location: 218 Kenler Dr., Bloomington IN 47408 Theme: Cocktail Party Food: &amp;ldquo;heavy hors d&amp;rsquo;oeuvres and excellent cocktails&amp;rdquo; Some hors D&amp;rsquo;oeuvres will be Vegetarian. If you have other dietary restrictions please contact Brad Schiesser below.  Long time BPP Supporters, Directors Circle Members, and friends Janet Stavropoulos and Michael Molenda are having a fantastic cocktail party at their lovely home near Griffy Lake. This is going to be a fantastic affair you won&amp;rsquo;t want to miss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Days of Dinner</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/lawson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/lawson/</guid>
      <description>Date: January 9th Time: 6:30PM Location: 703 S Fess Ave., Bloomington IN 47401 Theme: German Winter Party Food: &amp;ldquo;German food including Rindsrouladen and Späzle.&amp;rdquo; Wine provided by Oliver Winery. If you have other dietary restrictions please contact Brad Schiesser below.  Long time BPP Supporter, Directors Circle Member, and friend Julia Lawson will be hosting a dinner party of German food and fun. Julia who still teaches Germanic Studies will be guiding you through a fantastic German meal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Days of Dinner</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/esther_chad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/esther_chad/</guid>
      <description>Date: January 6th Time: 6:30PM Location: 3714 E Rachels Glen Rd., Bloomington IN 47408 Theme: Game Night! Food: Hors d&amp;rsquo;oeuvres and party snacks (some vegetarian friendly). Beer, wine and nonalcoholic beverages will be provided. Wine provided by the BPP.  BPP Board member Esther Smail and BPP Artistic Director Chad Rabinovitz are combining forces to give you a fantastic night of fun, games, and food. With Chad acting as game master and Esther getting fabulous food together this is going to be a night you won&amp;rsquo;t soon forget.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Days of Dinner</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/beebe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2019 17:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/beebe/</guid>
      <description>Date: January 5th Time: 5:30PM Dinner at 6:30PM Location: 1100 Brummetts Creek Rd, Bloomington IN 47408 Theme: Dinner Party Food: &amp;ldquo;A tour of Mexican Cuisine&amp;rdquo; Host open to dietary restrictions available with Wine provided by Oliver Winery  Longtime friend, subscriber, and supporter of BPP, Caroline Beebe, will be hosting a dinner party at her GORGEOUS home near Yellowwood State Forest only a ten minute drive from downtown Bloomington.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Days of Dinner</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/brantlinger/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 17:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/brantlinger/</guid>
      <description>Date: January 4th Time: 5PM Location: Bell Trace Theme: Dinner Party Food: A fantastic dinner prepared by Pat.  BPP Board member Pat Brantlinger is hosting a special dinner party at his home in Bell Trace.
THIS DINNER EVENT IS SOLD OUT
Price: $50</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>