<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>comedy on Bloomington Playwrights Project</title>
    <link>http://newplays.org/genres/comedy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in comedy on Bloomington Playwrights Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 19:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://newplays.org/genres/comedy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Oregon Trail</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/the-oregon-trail/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/the-oregon-trail/</guid>
      <description>13 year-old Jane has always had trouble making choices. Looking for an escape, she seeks refuge in the classic ‘80s video game, “The Oregon Trail” — where the choices are clear, the results are sure, and there’s always another life to live (after everyone dies of dysentery). But as time blurs, the boundaries between game and reality become hazy, until Jane finds herself leaping headfirst into the world of The Oregon Trail, where she’s forced to confront the choices she’s made, connect with her family, keep her oxen safe, and ford the river of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beating A Dead Horse</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/beating-a-dead-horse/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/beating-a-dead-horse/</guid>
      <description>Brothers Steve and Marty Martin are on the brink of closing their failing pet funeral home, until an eccentric (and rich) new customer comes in with an amazing proposition: plan a funeral for her nearly dead racehorse, and she’ll give the boys a fortune to keep their business afloat. The only problem? The horse won’t die. With everything on the line, the two embark on a hysterical journey to see how far they’ll go to make their dreams come true, in this laugh-a-minute screwball comedy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Row After Row</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/row-after-row/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/row-after-row/</guid>
      <description>Historical accuracy is paramount to Cal and Tom, two hardcore Civil War re-enactors, fresh off their latest Gettysburg battle. But their accuracy is compromised when they’re joined by a soldier with a less than authentic confederate uniform&amp;hellip; and the wrong gender. Straddling 1863 and today, ROW AFTER ROW is a dark comedy about choosing your cause and finding your courage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Day Mourning Period</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/30-day-mourning-period/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/30-day-mourning-period/</guid>
      <description>Larry, Susan and Craig are locked in mind-numbing sales jobs that are slowly draining each of them. But everything changes when their boss, Mr. Clybourne, kills himself one morning, and their company grants the office a 30-day &amp;ldquo;mourning period&amp;rdquo; with no sales goals, no dress codes and no corporate oversight. With a newfound freedom and an unbridled sense of adventure, the three thrust themselves into their own tale of rebellion, and over the course of their mourning period they build a castle out of office supplies, encounter an army of rats, fight with water balloons, drink excessive amounts of tequila, discover meaning in their previously meaningless monotony and ultimately attempt to right the wrongs of their company’s impersonal policies in their own makeshift revolution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Billy Witch</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2015-2016/billy-witch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2015 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2015-2016/billy-witch/</guid>
      <description>Oliver is hoping that summer camp will change him. Somewhere in the bizarre mixture of secrets and s’mores; sexual exploration and swimming; ghosts, girls and god’s eyes; somewhere in all that mess&amp;hellip;Oliver just might grow up. Travel back to a time when we were all innocent in this riotously funny and disarmingly tender Reva Shiner Comedy Award winning play about the awkward (and often hysterical) transformation from youth to adolescence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Capables</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/the-capables/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/the-capables/</guid>
      <description>Anna Capable is a hoarder. The stacks of McDonald&amp;rsquo;s happy meal toys, beanie babies, and useless junk pile straight up to the ceiling, forcing her daughter, Jessy, to call a TV network in hopes of clearing the mess and curing her mother. But the TV network&amp;rsquo;s producer, David, is looking for more than just another cluttered home to get the ratings he needs. With his career on the line, he&amp;rsquo;s hungry to expose the Capables&amp;rsquo; dirty laundry &amp;ndash; whether it&amp;rsquo;s in their house, or their personal lives &amp;ndash; at all costs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greta</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/greta/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/greta/</guid>
      <description>In the exciting next phase of its evolution, Kissing Frogs, one of BPP&amp;rsquo;s best-selling shows ever, returns for its second draft with some new songs and an all-new story. It all happened at the Stop Drop &amp;amp; Bowl. At least that&amp;rsquo;s how Greta&amp;rsquo;s beginning to feel about every major event in her life. After college, Greta puts her future on hold to help her grandmother run the family bowling alley, the very same one she grew up in.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>