<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Bloomington Playwrights Project</title>
    <link>http://newplays.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Bloomington Playwrights Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2011 00:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://newplays.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>BPP&#39;s 41st Birthday Celebration</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2019-2020/bpps-birthday-bash/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 18:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2019-2020/bpps-birthday-bash/</guid>
      <description>After how much fun we had last year, BPP is throwing itself another Birthday Celebration in 2020! Start the night out at 6:30 with donated food, wine, and beer! Then move into the theatre for the announcement of our 2020-2021 Season and a staged reading of the 2011 SMASH HIT Still the River Runs starring the original cast (Gabe Gloden &amp;amp; Daniel J. Petrie). Then stick around for the announcement of the 2020-21 Season (our 41st!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Burdens</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/the-burdens/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/the-burdens/</guid>
      <description>Siblings Mordy and Jane communicate like proper millennials: primarily through text message and loaded with sarcasm. When their loving mother’s life becomes emotionally and financially taxed by their absolutely awful and 100-year-old grandfather, Zad-Zad, they draw together an elaborate plot to…relieve their mother’s burden. Told almost entirely via text messages, The Burdens is a dark, family comedy about how technology helps keep us close, while still enabling us to keep our distance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Absentee</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/the-absentee/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/the-absentee/</guid>
      <description>Far out in the Milky Way, “Beacons” serve as lighthouses for warping spaceships around the galaxy. When a U.S. Space Forces ship explodes near Beacon 44.AR.90, its Operator finds herself alone in deep space with only her ship’s AI for companionship. That is, until a persistent canvasser calls, desperate to convince her to vote absentee in the 2088 election.
Box office opens at 6:30pm, house opens at 7pm, shows begin at 7:30pm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Enlightenment of Percival Von Schmootz</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/percival-von-schmootz/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/percival-von-schmootz/</guid>
      <description>Fed up with a world filled with plagues, pestilence, and poor personal hygiene, a ridiculously optimistic young man sets out on a quest to end the Dark Ages. As he attempts to bring the light of hope to the world, Percival Von Schmootz meets with hilariously disastrous results at every turn. Yet in this outrageous, Monty Python-esque musical comedy, it is only when things look the darkest that Percival is able to discover what true enlightenment means, as he finds hope (and humor) in impossibly bleak circumstances.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lost Letters</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/lost-letters/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/lost-letters/</guid>
      <description>Newly married, newly moved, and with a newborn on the way, Adam is scrambling to get everything ready for the arrival of his daughter – all the while questioning the choices that brought him to this moment. While clearing out boxes from his soon-to-be nursery, he finds a trove of handwritten letters from his past. The letters come to life and force Adam to (finally) reply, make peace with the present, and embrace his new reality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ike &amp; Julie Arnove PlayOffs</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2019-2020/ike-and-julie-arnove-playoffs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2019-2020/ike-and-julie-arnove-playoffs/</guid>
      <description>Batter up for the Ike &amp;amp; Julie Arnove PlayOffs! It&amp;rsquo;s almost that time of year again when we separate the contenders from the pretenders, the pros from the joes, the heroes from the zeros. Yes, that’s right - the baseball playoffs are just around the corner. In celebration, the BPP is presenting its most electrifying, action-packed, and anticipated fundraising event of the year, the Ike &amp;amp; Julie Arnove PlayOffs!
Just what are The PlayOffs, you ask?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simon Coronel&#39;s Magic Smackdown</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2019-2020/simon-coronels-magic-smackdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2019 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2019-2020/simon-coronels-magic-smackdown/</guid>
      <description>Simon Coronel’s Magic Smackdown combines the amazing magic of Penn &amp;amp; Teller’s Fool Us, the humor and fun of Whose Line Is It Anyway, and the excitement of live voting you find on American Idol. This wholly original evening of entertainment stars award-winning stage and television magicians (and regulars of the Magic Castle) competing for both your attention and your affection. It’s an exhilarating and interactive magic show that will keep you laughing and amazed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mind Tricks with Max Major</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2019-2020/mind-tricks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2019-2020/mind-tricks/</guid>
      <description>World-renowned mentalist, Max Major, has given over 2,000 live performances and 100 television appearances. But after he baffled our minds at BPP in 2017 with his latest show, Max took a sudden and unexpected break from performing to focus on his most difficult trick yet: recovering from Lyme disease. Two years later, he’s traveling back to BPP to make his triumphant return to the stage and picking up where he left off, with a new outlook on life and incredible new feats of mind-reading and magic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rap Guide to Consciousness</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/rap-guide-to-conciousnes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/rap-guide-to-conciousnes/</guid>
      <description>PLEASE BE AWARE: Rap Guide to Consciousness and Rap Guide to Culture are SOLD SEPERATLY.
“Peer reviewed rapper” Baba Brinkman takes a deep dive into the neuroscience of human experience, from sensations to hallucinations. “Mind-blowingly, awe-inspiringly good”. (Broadway Baby) Baba’s brain consists of tens of billions of neurons, none of which has any idea that he exists. And yet, somehow, those cells come together to produce a steady stream of ill rhymes, laughs, and revelations about the mind we live in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rap Guide to Culture</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/rap-guide-to-culture/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2019 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/rap-guide-to-culture/</guid>
      <description>PLEASE BE AWARE: Rap Guide to Consciousness and Rap Guide to Culture are SOLD SEPERATLY.
Music, poetry, art, science, politics, and relationships are all strange behaviors found in a species of (mostly) hairless primates. How do norms and social systems evolve, and who benefits? The whole planet hangs in the balance as cultures and sub-cultures compete for survival and the reach to become viral. Equal parts rap concert, TED Talk, and stand-up gig, Rap Guide to Culture surprises, delights, and ultimately heals, bringing a wealth of knowledge and razor-sharp observational wit to some of today’s stickiest topics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Check out our Summer Camp Offerings</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/special/bpp-education-camps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 19:08:09 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/special/bpp-education-camps/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BPP&#39;s 40th Birthday Celebration</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/vintage-songs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 18:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/vintage-songs/</guid>
      <description>This June 6th, we are throwing ourselves a 40th Birthday Celebration! Start the night out at 6:30 with donated food, wine, and beer! Then move into the theatre for the announcement of our 2019-2020 Season and a staged read of the 2014 SMASH HIT Kalamazoo. Join the original cast and relive the wonderful story of BPP&amp;rsquo;s best selling show of all time. Then stick around for the announcement of the 2019-20 Season (our 40th!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To Quiet the Quiet</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2018-2019/to-quiet-the-quiet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2018-2019/to-quiet-the-quiet/</guid>
      <description>From the writer of the hit musical Home.
Having suffered great loss and heartbreak, Kathy is a woman on the edge. Haunted by her past and her own personal demons, Kathy seems to be losing the battle against her thoughts, her words, and her fears. And the one man who can help her may prove to be just as powerless against her…
Contains violence and may not be suitable for all ages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Jedi Handbook</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2018-2019/the-jedi-handbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2018-2019/the-jedi-handbook/</guid>
      <description>A not so long time ago, in a theater not so far away, came a film that rocked the galaxy – changing both cinema and schoolyards forever…
The Jedi Handbook is a coming of age story about a young boy who survives growing older with help from The Force. Experiencing the Star Wars franchise anew, through the eyes and imagination of a kid, The Jedi Handbook takes us on a nostalgic journey back to an era we can all relate to – our childhood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Days of Dinner</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/spier_ellenwood/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/spier_ellenwood/</guid>
      <description>Date: January 31st Time: 6PM Location: 2110 E Covenanter Dr., Bloomington IN 47401 Theme: Venetian Masquerade Mystery Party Food: There will be 5 courses to the meal including drinks. Attire: Cocktail - Please wear something black, green and/or blue Mask: Required - There will be a prize for the best mask Childcare: Babysitting at the event can be provided for an additional $15. Children will be downstairs the whole party with the sitter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Days of Dinner</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/butler/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/butler/</guid>
      <description>Date: January 26th Time: 6PM Location: 4249 S Clear View Dr, Bloomington IN 47403 Theme: Melting Pot Party Food: Wide assortment of foods cooked around a communal melting pot. Host open to dietary restrictions (contact Brad Schiesser below if you have dietary restrictions) available with Wine provided by Oliver Winery  Longtime friend, subscriber, Playoff Director, and supporter of BPP, Sheila Butler and Prince Butler will be hosting a dinner party at their home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Days of Dinner</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/johnson_solberg/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/johnson_solberg/</guid>
      <description>Date: January 25th Time: 6PM Location: 344 S Rogers St, Bloomington IN 47403 Theme: Scandinavian delights Food: A sit down dinner of Scandinavian cuisine, from the Scandinavian Hostess with the Mostest Sonja Johnson  Long time donors, volunteers, and BPP Angels Sonja Johnson and Keith Solberg are opening up their home for yet another fantastic mini-party! Their get togethers are BPP lore and we don&amp;rsquo;t want you to miss out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Days of Dinner</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/michaelsens/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/michaelsens/</guid>
      <description>Date: January 25th Time: 5:30 PM (Will begin promptly to allow for actors and attendees to be at the performance that evening) Location: 2605 E Seminary Dr., Bloomington IN 47401 Theme: Cocktail Party Food: Cocktails and heavy hor d’ouvres at their fabulous home. If you have dietary restrictions please contact Brad Schiesser below.  Director for our upcoming production of APROPOS OF NOTHING Jonathan Michaelsen and his wife Miah, the Deputy Director of the Indiana Arts Commission, are opening up their amazing home to guests wanting to support BPP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Days of Dinner</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/spier_arnove/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/spier_arnove/</guid>
      <description>Date: January 25th Time: Sunset Location: 2110 E Covenanter Dr., Bloomington IN 47401 Theme: Special Shabbat Dinner Food: Traditional Friday Sabbath meal with wine Childcare: Babysitting at the event can be provided for an additional $15. Children will be downstairs the whole party with the sitter.  Board members Ellee Spier and Bob Arnove invite you to a very special Shabbat Dinner in support of the BPP. The event will be at Ellee&amp;rsquo;s home on Covenanter Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Days of Dinner</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/welch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/welch/</guid>
      <description>Date: January 24th Time: 5:30-7:30PM Location: 1211 S. Walnut St, Bloomington IN 47401 Theme: Mead Tasting! Food: &amp;ldquo;Catered in food as well as mead tastings from Oddball Fermentables&amp;rdquo; Some food will be Vegetarian. If you have other dietary restrictions please contact Brad Schiesser below.  BPP Board member Von Welch and Oddball Fermentables are teaming up to bring you this special opportunity to support BPP and enjoy the local crafted mead from right here in Bloomington.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Days of Dinner</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/susan_jones/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/susan_jones/</guid>
      <description>Date: January 22nd Time: 6PM Location: 3508 E William Ct., Bloomington IN 47401 Theme: Moroccan themed dinner Party Food: Moroccan main course with Vegetarian option.  Long time BPP Supporters/Directors Circle Members/Guardian Angels Susan and David Jones are having a fantastic Dinner party at their lovely home on the South side. Moroccan food will be served and a fun BPP game will accompany the meal. This is going to be a fantastic affair you won&amp;rsquo;t want to miss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Days of Dinner</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/daily/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/daily/</guid>
      <description>Date: January 20th Time: 6PM Location: 3512 S Tudor Ln., Bloomington IN 47401 Theme: FAMILY NIGHT Food: &amp;ldquo;Whatever the kids decide to make that night&amp;rdquo;  BPP Board member and Artistic Director of the John Waldron Arts Center Paul Daily will be opening up his home so the whole family can be a part of this experience. Not only will Paul&amp;rsquo;s lovely wife Courtney be there but also their 3 children who will be acting as chefs and servers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Days of Dinner</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/sideli/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/sideli/</guid>
      <description>Date: January 26th Time: 6PM Location: 1410 E University, Bloomington IN 47401 Theme: Dinner Party Food: A fantastic sit down dinner. Wine provided by Oliver Winery  Longtime BPP supporter Kathy Sideli will be having a dinner party at her home
THIS DINNER IS SOLD OUT
Price: $50</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apropos of Nothing</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2018-2019/apropos-of-nothing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2018-2019/apropos-of-nothing/</guid>
      <description>Owen confesses, apropos of nothing, that he’s in love with his best friend’s wife.
But it’s just “a passing phase,” he tells him. “Forget I even said it.” Unfortunately, no one can. And now that it’s out there, everyone’s lives are turned upside-down, and no one’s relationship is safe from the wreckage. In a comedy about love, irony, and cliché, five people struggle with…well…love, irony, and cliché.
Contains adult language and situations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Days of Dinner</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/shakalis_bright/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/shakalis_bright/</guid>
      <description>Date: January 17th Time: 6:30PM Location: 3207 E Kristen Ct., Bloomington IN 47401 Theme: &amp;ldquo;Sparkling Midwinter Spontaneity.” E.g., “Please bring to show — or wear — something sparkly that evokes memories for you. (Or, not.)&amp;rdquo; Food: &amp;ldquo;chicken dish, hor d’ouvres, dessert, bread, beer, wine, salad, etc.&amp;rdquo; If you have dietary restrictions please contact Brad Schiesser below.  Herald Times Arts Reviewer Connie Shakalis (Vicky Richards in TUNING IN) and Long time BPP Supporter, Directors Circle Members, and play reader Anne Bright, invite you to a dinner party that will put some shine into the dreary month of January.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Days of Dinner</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/martin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/martin/</guid>
      <description>Date: January 17th Time: 6PM Location: 2368 Winding Brook Circle, Bloomington IN 47401 Theme: Dinner Party Food: &amp;ldquo;Indian Cuisine&amp;rdquo; with Vegetarian options available. If you have other dietary restrictions please contact Brad Schiesser below.  BPP Board member David Martin will be hosting a dinner of Indian cuisine. David a talented cook himeself will make a fantastic meal that will transport you to the subcontinent. You don&amp;rsquo;t want to miss this one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Days of Dinner</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/shakespeare/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/shakespeare/</guid>
      <description>Date: January 16th Time: 5:30-7 Location: 1806 E Thornton Dr., Bloomington IN 47401 Theme: Wine Tasting Food: &amp;ldquo;Appetizers paired with several incredible wines from around the world&amp;rdquo;  BPP board member Rob Shakespeare and his wife (longtime BPP supporter) Marie will be hosting a Pinot Noir Wine Tasting with selections from famous regions. The tasting will be paired with delicious appetizers at their home.
THIS DINNER IS SOLD OUT</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Days of Dinner</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/engber/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/engber/</guid>
      <description>Date: January 13th Time: 6PM Location: 2731 S Silver Creek Dr., Bloomington IN 47401 Theme: Tapas From Around the World Food: Tapas from Around the World including Spain, Greece, and Japan. Some Tapas will be Vegetarian. If you have other dietary restrictions please contact Brad Schiesser below  BPP Board member Michael Engber and his wife Cheryl (both longtime supporters) will be hosting a culinary delight at their home with a series of small plates or Tapas from around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Days of Dinner</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/ted_jones/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/ted_jones/</guid>
      <description>Date: January 13th Time: 4:30PM Location: 1607 S Woodruff Ln., Bloomington IN 47401 Theme: Curated Wine Tasting Food: &amp;ldquo;Heavy hors D&amp;rsquo;oeuvres, some of which will be Vegetarian, and a selection of wines to taste.  This one is not to be missed! Ted Jones (The one whose name is on the side of the BPP Building) is hosting a curated wine tasting with passed hors D&amp;rsquo;oeuvres at his fabulous home in Bloomington.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Days of Dinner</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/freund/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/freund/</guid>
      <description>Date: January 12th Time: 6PM Location: 2100 S. Olcott Blvd., Bloomington IN 47401 Theme: &amp;ldquo;Theatre Charades&amp;rdquo; Food: A sumptuous dinner with Wine provided by Oliver Winery  BPP Board President Sandra Freund and her husband Don will be hosting theatre charades and a fantastic sit down dinner.
THIS DINNER IS SOLD OUT
Price: $50</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Days of Dinner</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/stavropoulos_molenda/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/stavropoulos_molenda/</guid>
      <description>Date: January 11th Time: 6PM Location: 218 Kenler Dr., Bloomington IN 47408 Theme: Cocktail Party Food: &amp;ldquo;heavy hors d&amp;rsquo;oeuvres and excellent cocktails&amp;rdquo; Some hors D&amp;rsquo;oeuvres will be Vegetarian. If you have other dietary restrictions please contact Brad Schiesser below.  Long time BPP Supporters, Directors Circle Members, and friends Janet Stavropoulos and Michael Molenda are having a fantastic cocktail party at their lovely home near Griffy Lake. This is going to be a fantastic affair you won&amp;rsquo;t want to miss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Days of Dinner</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/lawson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/lawson/</guid>
      <description>Date: January 9th Time: 6:30PM Location: 703 S Fess Ave., Bloomington IN 47401 Theme: German Winter Party Food: &amp;ldquo;German food including Rindsrouladen and Späzle.&amp;rdquo; Wine provided by Oliver Winery. If you have other dietary restrictions please contact Brad Schiesser below.  Long time BPP Supporter, Directors Circle Member, and friend Julia Lawson will be hosting a dinner party of German food and fun. Julia who still teaches Germanic Studies will be guiding you through a fantastic German meal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Days of Dinner</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/esther_chad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/esther_chad/</guid>
      <description>Date: January 6th Time: 6:30PM Location: 3714 E Rachels Glen Rd., Bloomington IN 47408 Theme: Game Night! Food: Hors d&amp;rsquo;oeuvres and party snacks (some vegetarian friendly). Beer, wine and nonalcoholic beverages will be provided. Wine provided by the BPP.  BPP Board member Esther Smail and BPP Artistic Director Chad Rabinovitz are combining forces to give you a fantastic night of fun, games, and food. With Chad acting as game master and Esther getting fabulous food together this is going to be a night you won&amp;rsquo;t soon forget.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Days of Dinner</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/beebe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2019 17:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/beebe/</guid>
      <description>Date: January 5th Time: 5:30PM Dinner at 6:30PM Location: 1100 Brummetts Creek Rd, Bloomington IN 47408 Theme: Dinner Party Food: &amp;ldquo;A tour of Mexican Cuisine&amp;rdquo; Host open to dietary restrictions available with Wine provided by Oliver Winery  Longtime friend, subscriber, and supporter of BPP, Caroline Beebe, will be hosting a dinner party at her GORGEOUS home near Yellowwood State Forest only a ten minute drive from downtown Bloomington.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Days of Dinner</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/brantlinger/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 17:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/brantlinger/</guid>
      <description>Date: January 4th Time: 5PM Location: Bell Trace Theme: Dinner Party Food: A fantastic dinner prepared by Pat.  BPP Board member Pat Brantlinger is hosting a special dinner party at his home in Bell Trace.
THIS DINNER EVENT IS SOLD OUT
Price: $50</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tuning In</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2018-2019/tuning-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2018-2019/tuning-in/</guid>
      <description>All is peaceful at the Harmony Hill retirement community – the rooms are comfy, the meals are tasty, and the citizen-run radio station is a hit (even if it only plays hits from the past). But when an executive waltzes in threatening to take over WLK 89.3 and turn it into a contemporary music station, the talented tenants of the senior center band together and hold a radiothon to keep it alive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ike &amp; Julie Arnove PlayOffs</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/ike-and-julie-arnove-playoffs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/ike-and-julie-arnove-playoffs/</guid>
      <description>Batter up for the Ike &amp;amp; Julie Arnove PlayOffs! It&amp;rsquo;s almost that time of year again when we separate the contenders from the pretenders, the pros from the joes, the heroes from the zeros. Yes, that’s right - the baseball playoffs are just around the corner. In celebration, the BPP is presenting its most electrifying, action-packed, and anticipated fundraising event of the year, the Ike &amp;amp; Julie Arnove PlayOffs!
Just what are The PlayOffs, you ask?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glitches in Reality</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2018-2019/glitches-in-reality/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2018-2019/glitches-in-reality/</guid>
      <description>From the mind of renowned Australian magician, Simon Coronel, comes an evening filled with astonishing and impossible events. Glitches in Reality uses close-up trickery and mind-blowing sleight of hand to take the audience on a journey through the truth behind magic and illusion; a truth that is far more amazing than even the illusions themselves.
Winner of over a dozen international awards including multiple from the prestigious World Championships of Magic, Simon is a regular performer at the Magic Castle and is a university lecturer on perception and illusion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Your Marc</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/on-your-marc-screening/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/on-your-marc-screening/</guid>
      <description>Do you remember back in 2016 when beloved TV icon, Marc Summers, premiered his one-man show Everything in Its Place: The Life and Slimes of Marc Summers at BPP? We sure do. Well, while that was going on, a documentary crew was filming.
Fast forward 2 years&amp;hellip; Surprise! Marc is joining us again this fall for a sneak preview screening of the completed film! On Your Marc intimately captures his life, career, and legacy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cook Group</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/sponsor/cook-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 14:04:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/sponsor/cook-group/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vintage Songs</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2017-2018/vintage-songs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 18:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2017-2018/vintage-songs/</guid>
      <description>This June, we invite you to expand your dramatic palate with an all-new show featuring a performance of favorite songs from BPP&amp;rsquo;s original musicals, as well as the announcement of the 2018-19 Season. The evening begins Thursday, June 14, 2018 with a full buffet dinner at 6:30pm, followed by the performances at 7:30pm. A cash bar with wine will also be open. This year we’ll be at the Oliver Winery Creekbend Vineyard at 7508 N Woodall Road, in Ellettsville.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Oregon Trail</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/the-oregon-trail/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/the-oregon-trail/</guid>
      <description>13 year-old Jane has always had trouble making choices. Looking for an escape, she seeks refuge in the classic ‘80s video game, “The Oregon Trail” — where the choices are clear, the results are sure, and there’s always another life to live (after everyone dies of dysentery). But as time blurs, the boundaries between game and reality become hazy, until Jane finds herself leaping headfirst into the world of The Oregon Trail, where she’s forced to confront the choices she’s made, connect with her family, keep her oxen safe, and ford the river of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out of Orbit</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/out-of-orbit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/out-of-orbit/</guid>
      <description>Sara, one of the world’s most brilliant planetary geologists, lives her life on Mars time — her days lasting longer and longer as she monitors mankind’s latest voyage to the Red Planet. But her daughter, Lis, continues to live her life as a teenager on Earth time, showing no interest in her mother’s world out in space—despite Sara’s best efforts. As both of their lives begin to spin out of control, they must grapple with the distance their two time zones create between them… even when they’re standing side by side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spun: A Brother/Sister Rock Musical</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/spun/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/spun/</guid>
      <description>Back by popular demand, one of BPP’s most beloved musicals returns with 6 new songs and some new surprises in store. Don’t miss this encore performance as it prepares for an anticipated NYC run!
Following their father’s death, Molly and her estranged brother Jesse come home to pick up the pieces. But as they begin to recount their childhood together, two very different stories are revealed… and rock-n-roll tears through the past to uncover wounds that still must be healed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Front Page Flo</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/front-page-flo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/front-page-flo/</guid>
      <description>In post-WWII New York City, the newspaper is king, and rambunctious reporter Flo is hungry for her big break. So when word hits the wires that a Soviet spy has landed in Manhattan, Flo follows the clues to get the scoop — and discovers more than she bargained for. With a golden-era Broadway score, dazzling dance numbers, loves lost (and found again), and non-stop fun, FRONT PAGE FLO is the world premiere musical that feels like seeing a classic for the very first time!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ike &amp; Julie Arnove Playoffs</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2017-2018/ike-and-julie-arnove-playoffs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2017 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2017-2018/ike-and-julie-arnove-playoffs/</guid>
      <description>Donate to the 2017 Ike &amp;amp; Julie Arnove PlayOffs!
It’s that time of the year again for the Ike &amp;amp; Julie Arnove PlayOffs. The time of year when we separate the contenders from the pretenders, the pros from the joes, the heroes from the zeros. Yes, that’s right, the baseball playoffs are just around the corner. In celebration, the BPP is presenting its most electrifying, action-packed, and anticipated fundraising event of the year, the Ike &amp;amp; Julie Arnove PlayOffs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beating A Dead Horse</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/beating-a-dead-horse/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/beating-a-dead-horse/</guid>
      <description>Brothers Steve and Marty Martin are on the brink of closing their failing pet funeral home, until an eccentric (and rich) new customer comes in with an amazing proposition: plan a funeral for her nearly dead racehorse, and she’ll give the boys a fortune to keep their business afloat. The only problem? The horse won’t die. With everything on the line, the two embark on a hysterical journey to see how far they’ll go to make their dreams come true, in this laugh-a-minute screwball comedy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*check out* our brand new *season* lineup</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/special/new-works/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2017 16:03:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/special/new-works/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tickets</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/tickets/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 08:34:12 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/tickets/</guid>
      <description>For tickets, contact the BCT Box Office at 812.323.3020 or visit them at 114 E. Kirkwood, next to the Buskirk-Chumley Theater.
Tickets for most BPP shows are also available for purchase at the door the night of the event and online.
Individual Performances  General Admission - $25 Students - $15  Buy Tickets Online
Season Subscription Subscribe to the BPP Main Stage Series and receive these benefits with your Subscription:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vintage Songs</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2016-2017/vintage-songs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 18:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2016-2017/vintage-songs/</guid>
      <description>This June, we invite you to expand your dramatic palate with an all-new show featuring a performance of favorite songs from BPP&amp;rsquo;s original musicals, as well as the announcement of the 2018-19 Season. The evening begins Thursday, June 14, 2018 with a full buffet dinner at 6:30pm, followed by the performances at 7:30pm. A cash bar with wine will also be open. This year we’ll be at the Oliver Winery Creekbend Vineyard at 7508 N Woodall Road, in Ellettsville.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happily After Ever</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/happily-after-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/happily-after-ever/</guid>
      <description>Newlyweds Darren and Janet want nothing more than to build the perfect life together. But when Janet gives birth to a baby with both male and female genitalia, they find themselves in the unlikely position of having to choose a gender for their child - all while competing with the perfect couple next door and dealing with a misunderstood family dog - in this hilarious battle of the sexes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miniplay Playwriting Competition</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2016-2017/miniplay-playwriting-competition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2017 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2016-2017/miniplay-playwriting-competition/</guid>
      <description>2016 Winners  Jack Nelson, Grade 6, University Elementary School Hunter S.W. Broomall, Grade 4, University Elementary School Jack Knudsen, Grade 3, Unionville Elementary School Wilson Lommel, Grade 4, Unionville Elementary School Dahlia Ritter, Grade 6, Childs Elementary School Sandro Smith, Grade 6, University Elementary School  2017 Event The winning plays will be performed by local actors on Sunday, April 9th! Admittance will be granted with a first-come first-serve basis with limited seating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calling All Kates</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/calling-all-kates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2017 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/calling-all-kates/</guid>
      <description>Marc gets dumped by his fiancé, Kate McBride, right before their wedding and honeymoon around the world. He’s now single and left to travel the globe alone since his plane tickets are non-transferrable and non-refundable. In an act of desperation, Marc posts an ad online for the only companion who could legally join him&amp;hellip; someone with the exact same name as his ex-fiancé. Set loose in a bunch of different foreign countries, strangers Marc and Kate must get to know one another and learn to get along in the wake of Marc&amp;rsquo;s heartbreak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Style Guide</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/style-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2017 09:36:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/style-guide/</guid>
      <description>Colors $white $gray-light $gray $gray-dark $black $primary-dark $primary $primary-light $accent Typography Headings  h1. The spectacle before us was indeed sublime. h2. The spectacle before us was indeed sublime. h3. The spectacle before us was indeed sublime. h4. The spectacle before us was indeed sublime. h5. The spectacle before us was indeed sublime. h6. The spectacle before us was indeed sublime.  Paragraphs Apparently we had reached a great height in the atmosphere, for the sky was a dead black, and the stars had ceased to twinkle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Escape the Room</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2016-2017/escape-the-room/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2017 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2016-2017/escape-the-room/</guid>
      <description>You are a member of the IU Basketball team and you’ve been locked in Tom Crean’s office by the evil Boilermakers. If you don’t find a way to get out, IU will have to forfeit and Purdue will win the big game. The stakes are high – but will you escape in time?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Row After Row</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/row-after-row/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/row-after-row/</guid>
      <description>Historical accuracy is paramount to Cal and Tom, two hardcore Civil War re-enactors, fresh off their latest Gettysburg battle. But their accuracy is compromised when they’re joined by a soldier with a less than authentic confederate uniform&amp;hellip; and the wrong gender. Straddling 1863 and today, ROW AFTER ROW is a dark comedy about choosing your cause and finding your courage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/home/</guid>
      <description>Katherine escaped from her small Texas home and her hypochondriac mother 9 years ago. When she finally steps back into her childhood home, Katherine is immediately overwhelmed by the familiar. Every room seems to have a story. Every corner of the house holds another recollection. Katherine’s memories become so vivid, in fact, they appear to come alive before her eyes. Both humorous and heartbreaking, HOME explores parenting and childhood with unflinching honesty, questioning what it means to grow older, and whether we truly have the capacity to grow up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ike &amp; Julie Arnove Playoffs</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2016-2017/ike-and-julie-arnove-playoffs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2016-2017/ike-and-julie-arnove-playoffs/</guid>
      <description>Donate to the 2016 Ike &amp;amp; Julie Arnove PlayOffs!
It’s that time of the year again for the Ike &amp;amp; Julie Arnove PlayOffs. The time of year when we separate the contenders from the pretenders, the pros from the joes, the heroes from the zeros. Yes, that’s right, the baseball playoffs are just around the corner. In celebration, the BPP is presenting its most electrifying, action-packed, and anticipated fundraising event of the year, the Ike &amp;amp; Julie Arnove PlayOffs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Involved</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/get-involved/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 08:34:12 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/get-involved/</guid>
      <description>The BPP relies heavily on the support and contribution of volunteers to produce its high-quality productions. We work with an average of over 40 volunteers and interns who assist with everything from hanging posters to working on a backstage crew. We also hold open auditions to the public and work with many artists from within the Bloomington area.
You can always call 812.334.1188 or e-mail bppwrite@newplays.org for information about how you can support the development of new plays in Bloomington.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Day Mourning Period</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/30-day-mourning-period/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/30-day-mourning-period/</guid>
      <description>Larry, Susan and Craig are locked in mind-numbing sales jobs that are slowly draining each of them. But everything changes when their boss, Mr. Clybourne, kills himself one morning, and their company grants the office a 30-day &amp;ldquo;mourning period&amp;rdquo; with no sales goals, no dress codes and no corporate oversight. With a newfound freedom and an unbridled sense of adventure, the three thrust themselves into their own tale of rebellion, and over the course of their mourning period they build a castle out of office supplies, encounter an army of rats, fight with water balloons, drink excessive amounts of tequila, discover meaning in their previously meaningless monotony and ultimately attempt to right the wrongs of their company’s impersonal policies in their own makeshift revolution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Woodward/Newman Drama Award</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/submit-a-play/woodward-newman-drama/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2016 08:20:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/submit-a-play/woodward-newman-drama/</guid>
      <description>The Woodward/Newman Drama Award is an exclusive honor offered by Bloomington Playwrights Project, remembering the many great dramas Joanne Woodward and Paul Newman performed in together.
It presents the best unpublished full-length drama of the year with a cash prize of $3,000 and a full production as part of the BPP&amp;rsquo;s Mainstage season, along with travel reimbursement. Submissions for the 2020-21 competition must be postmarked by Dec 1, 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reva Shiner Comedy Award</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/submit-a-play/reva-shiner-comedy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2016 13:14:50 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/submit-a-play/reva-shiner-comedy/</guid>
      <description>The Reva Shiner Comedy Award presents an unpublished full-length comedy with a cash prize of $1,000, a full production as part of the Bloomington Playwrights Project&amp;rsquo;s Mainstage season, along with travel reimbursement. We are currently accepting submissions for the 2020-21 Season. Scripts must be postmarked by October 31, 2019.
Previous winners have gone on to enjoy productions around the world and to garner additional honors such as the National Play Award.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MiniPlay Playwriting Contest</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/education/miniplay-playwriting-contest/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2016 11:54:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/education/miniplay-playwriting-contest/</guid>
      <description>The highly successful and long-running MiniPlay Contest invites students in 1st-8th grades to participate and write a short play on the topic of EXPLORERS. 1st, 2nd, and 3rd place MiniPlay winners will receive public recognition and a staged reading (April 5, 2020) of their winning play by local actors at a special MiniPlay Premiere Party with Ice Cream and Pizza! Plus NEW THIS YEAR, Grand Prize winners in each category will also receive a $50 cash prize!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>After School EdVentures</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/education/after-school-edventures/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2016 11:54:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/education/after-school-edventures/</guid>
      <description>The BPP offers drama clubs for elementary students through the After School EdVentures program.
Where? These clubs take place at Fairview, Templeton, Arlington Heights, Grandview, Summit, and Highland Park elementary schools.
What? When? Students in drama club learn and practice using the actors&amp;rsquo; tools of body, voice and imagination and develop skills to work creatively and collaboratively through improvisation and creative dramatics. K-2 students adapt a story, and older students collaborate on short skits for performance at the final class.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musical Theater Camp</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/education/musical-theater-camp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2016 11:54:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/education/musical-theater-camp/</guid>
      <description>Ages 9 - 16 July 8 - July 26, 2019 Performances July 26 and 27 at 7pm Monday - Friday; 9am - 4pm, $395 Register today! Email education@newplays.org for more info.  Campers will work with BPP professionals to write and produce an exciting new musical starring them! Students will start by learning about - and singing songs from - popular Broadway musicals. They&amp;rsquo;ll train as actors, singers, dancers, playwrights, and designers as they learn every element that goes into putting on a show.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laugh Factory</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/education/laugh-factory/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2016 11:53:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/education/laugh-factory/</guid>
      <description>Ages 9 - 13 June 24 - July 5, 2019 Performances July 5 and 6 at 7pm 9am - 4pm $325 Register today! Email education@newplays.org for more info.  Do you have a funny kid at the dinner table? Do they practice their jokes for you hours on end or stay up late to watch Saturday Night Live? Then send them over to BPP’s Laugh Factory where they’ll learn to perfect their comedic acting, joke writing, and improv abilities!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DramatiKIDS</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/education/dramatikids/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2016 11:53:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/education/dramatikids/</guid>
      <description>Ages 8 - 12 $295 June 10 - June 21, 2019 performances June 21 and 22 at 7pm Monday - Friday; 9am - 4pm Register today! Email education@newplays.org for more info.   A virtual playground for young imaginations, DramatiKIDS is the perfect opportunity for young actors and writers to explore their creativity, learning skills in both acting and playwriting, culminating in an opportunity to star in a play they write themselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Broadway Kids</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/education/broadway-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2016 11:53:09 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/education/broadway-kids/</guid>
      <description>Ages 5-8 Session 1: May 27 - May 31, 2019 - $200 (Please note: Day 1 is Memorial Day, but attendance is optional) performance on May 31 at 7PM Session 2: June 3 - June 7, 2019 - $200 Register for both sessions for $350 Monday - Friday; 9am - 4pm Register today! Email education@newplays.org for more info.  Participants will explore the world of theatre through music, movement, visual arts, and performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annual Gala</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2016-2017/annual-gala/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2016 18:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2016-2017/annual-gala/</guid>
      <description>The BPP Annual Gala will be a lively, classy evening! Cocktail hour will take place in three different areas from 6:30-7:30. And the dry ice cocktails are back by popular demand! You&amp;rsquo;ll be able to mingle, bid on silent auction items, and check out the delicious appetizers and beverages! The main event takes place in the auditorium from 7:30 - 10:00 and will feature entertainment by magician Caleb Wiles, as well as the live auction and an amazing dinner from IMU Catering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>jessica reed</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/bio/jessica-reed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2016 07:52:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/bio/jessica-reed/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chad Rabinovitz</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/bio/chad-rabinovitz/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2016 07:52:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/bio/chad-rabinovitz/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facility Rentals</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/facility-rentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 18:21:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/facility-rentals/</guid>
      <description>The BPP&amp;rsquo;s Ted Jones Playhouse boasts one of the most versatile rental spaces in Bloomington for anything from a theatre, dance performances, and film festivals to birthday parties, holiday events, and business meetings. BPP aims to keep our beautifully renovated, handicap accessible building as multi-purpose and affordable as possible, to better serve the Bloomington community.
Our facility has a large, open-air lobby space housing a box office booth, concessions counter, art gallery, and the Lora Shiner Studio Stage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 18:01:31 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.
Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected. We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms and Conditions</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/terms-and-conditions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 17:56:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/terms-and-conditions/</guid>
      <description>By accessing this web site, you are agreeing to be bound by these web site Terms and Conditions of Use, all applicable laws and regulations, and agree that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws. If you do not agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing this site. The materials contained in this web site are protected by applicable copyright and trade mark law.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>German American Bank</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/sponsor/german-american-bank/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 14:05:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/sponsor/german-american-bank/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Storage Express</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/sponsor/storage-express/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 14:05:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/sponsor/storage-express/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World Arts Printing</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/sponsor/world-arts-printing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 14:05:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/sponsor/world-arts-printing/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IU Credit Union</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/sponsor/iu-credit-union/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 14:05:12 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/sponsor/iu-credit-union/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meadowood Retirement Community</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/sponsor/meadowood/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 14:05:12 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/sponsor/meadowood/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oliver Winery</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/sponsor/oliver-winery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 14:05:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/sponsor/oliver-winery/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Longs Landing Furniture</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/sponsor/longs-landing-furniture/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 14:04:54 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/sponsor/longs-landing-furniture/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bloom Magazine</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/sponsor/bloom-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 14:04:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/sponsor/bloom-magazine/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grant Street Inn</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/sponsor/grant-street-inn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 14:04:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/sponsor/grant-street-inn/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brown County Community Foundation</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/sponsor/brown-county-community-foundation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 14:04:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/sponsor/brown-county-community-foundation/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indiana Arts Commision</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/sponsor/indiana-arts-commission/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 14:04:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/sponsor/indiana-arts-commission/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Domino&#39;s</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/sponsor/dominos/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2016 09:49:30 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/sponsor/dominos/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ivy Tech Community College</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/sponsor/ivy-tech/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2016 07:49:25 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/sponsor/ivy-tech/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Information</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2016 08:34:12 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/contact/</guid>
      <description> Box Office Phone 812-323-3020
Administrative Office Phone 812-334-1188
Email bppwrite@newplays.org
Address 107 West 9th Street Bloomington, IN 47404
Map   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Support the BPP</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/support/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2016 08:34:12 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/support/</guid>
      <description>As a 501(c)3 not-for-profit organization, the BPP relies on donations from individuals and businesses as well as grants and special event fundraisers. Only a small percentage of our overall budget comes from ticket sales so we rely on your generous and warmhearted support to continue to serve the Bloomington and national theatre communities.
Call us at 812.334.1188 , email us at bppwrite@newplays.org, or use PayPal:
 Donate to the BPP   Productions The BPP produces five Mainstage shows each season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Remind Me of You</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2015-2016/you-remind-me-of-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2015-2016/you-remind-me-of-you/</guid>
      <description>Adele has abandoned her law school plans and her social life to take care of her addled father – a man who has trouble remembering who she is. A chance encounter with a musician named Vincent might just be the best thing to ever happen to her. The catch: Vincent has a rare neurological condition – he has face blindness. This season’s Woodward/Newman Drama Award winning play explores what it’s like to love without recognition and how two people might just keep each other from disappearing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everything in its Place</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2015-2016/everything-in-its-place/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2016 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2015-2016/everything-in-its-place/</guid>
      <description>You may know him from his time hosting Nickelodeon&amp;rsquo;s Double Dare and Food Network&amp;rsquo;s Unwrapped, or as the Producer of hits like Dinner:Impossible and Restaurant:Impossible, but now you get the chance to meet the real Marc Summers &amp;ndash; a man who&amp;rsquo;s led a fascinating life of fame and frustration. Everything in its Place is a guided tour through Marc&amp;rsquo;s life, from an early obsession with magic to his notable television career and his struggles with OCD.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toast</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2015-2016/toast/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2016 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2015-2016/toast/</guid>
      <description>Based on the novella by Rex Rose. When Tania comes back home to New Orleans, she’s got one thing on her mind: finishing the beautiful tattoo across her back. But she finds her favorite nightclub in dire need of repair, her ex-boyfriend is slowly dying, and her rag tag group of bohemian friends is constantly changing. Carner and Gregor, authors of BPP audience favorite ISLAND SONG, return with an electric new musical about love, The Big Easy, and the difference between living a temporary life and a permanent one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Billy Witch</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2015-2016/billy-witch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2015 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2015-2016/billy-witch/</guid>
      <description>Oliver is hoping that summer camp will change him. Somewhere in the bizarre mixture of secrets and s’mores; sexual exploration and swimming; ghosts, girls and god’s eyes; somewhere in all that mess&amp;hellip;Oliver just might grow up. Travel back to a time when we were all innocent in this riotously funny and disarmingly tender Reva Shiner Comedy Award winning play about the awkward (and often hysterical) transformation from youth to adolescence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bull, the Moon and the Coronet of Stars</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2015-2016/the-bull-the-moon-and-the-coronet-of-stars/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2015-2016/the-bull-the-moon-and-the-coronet-of-stars/</guid>
      <description>Marion tries not to fall for Michael, her handsome (and very married) co-worker. But as Marion and Michael become entangled in each other, the museum where they work comes under a mysterious, mythological attack. A beast is roaming through the halls; a beast that threatens to destroy Marion’s capacity for love and to leave her wondering if she ever wants to find it again. The U.S. premiere of an award-winning new Australian play, THE BULL, THE MOON AND THE CORONET OF STARS is a magical, passionate, and charming love story of mythic proportions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Capables</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/the-capables/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/the-capables/</guid>
      <description>Anna Capable is a hoarder. The stacks of McDonald&amp;rsquo;s happy meal toys, beanie babies, and useless junk pile straight up to the ceiling, forcing her daughter, Jessy, to call a TV network in hopes of clearing the mess and curing her mother. But the TV network&amp;rsquo;s producer, David, is looking for more than just another cluttered home to get the ratings he needs. With his career on the line, he&amp;rsquo;s hungry to expose the Capables&amp;rsquo; dirty laundry &amp;ndash; whether it&amp;rsquo;s in their house, or their personal lives &amp;ndash; at all costs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ugly Lies the Bone</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/ugly-lies-the-bone/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/ugly-lies-the-bone/</guid>
      <description>Female soldier, Jess, returns from war severely burned only to find her Floridian hometown decaying with the end of the space shuttle era. She moves in with her sister and struggles through immense pain to define a new sense of &amp;ldquo;normal&amp;rdquo; when all she wants is her old life back. Using virtual reality therapy, Jess builds a dream world of cooling snow to calm her mind as she desperately tries to restore her relationships, home, and all that was lost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Me Bad</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/make-me-bad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2015 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/make-me-bad/</guid>
      <description>by special arrangement with The Benge Group
What happens when you fall in love with a serial killer? This gritty and sexy musical thriller follows the story of Daisy Harris, a young woman stuck in a small town with a dead-end job, an overbearing mother, and a troubled past. Desperate to escape but with nowhere to go, Daisy looks for anything to break the monotony of her meaningless life. She meets charming and cryptic Max, just as a string of unexplained murders rocks the town.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>She Kills Monsters</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/she-kills-monsters/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2014 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/she-kills-monsters/</guid>
      <description>Agnes never paid much attention to her teenage sister, Tilly, who took refuge in the role-playing world. But when a tragedy strikes and Tilly is lost forever, Agnes goes searching in the one place she can still be found: her late sister&amp;rsquo;s Dungeons &amp;amp; Dragons notebook. With the help of the game store clerk, Chuck, Agnes dives into the fantastical world of fairies, ogres, dragons, and even blood thirsty cheerleaders, in an action-packed comedy that searches for the warrior&amp;hellip; and the geek&amp;hellip; within us all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kalamazoo</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/kalamazoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2014 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/kalamazoo/</guid>
      <description>When Peg, a 70-something, Irish Catholic bird lover meets Irving, a 70-something Jewish, metal detector-toting East Coaster on an online dating site, it feels like love at first click. But after their crazy margarita-filled first date, complete with body shots and morning-after tattoos, Peg and Irving find that they still have a little aging to do if they want to forget their past and move forward into a future together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greta</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/greta/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/greta/</guid>
      <description>In the exciting next phase of its evolution, Kissing Frogs, one of BPP&amp;rsquo;s best-selling shows ever, returns for its second draft with some new songs and an all-new story. It all happened at the Stop Drop &amp;amp; Bowl. At least that&amp;rsquo;s how Greta&amp;rsquo;s beginning to feel about every major event in her life. After college, Greta puts her future on hold to help her grandmother run the family bowling alley, the very same one she grew up in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mad Gravity</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/mad-gravity/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2014 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/mad-gravity/</guid>
      <description>Archie and Eudora have built a live studio audience in their living room. Being constantly observed helps them to lead an honest and honorable life. But things get awkward when some important visitors get a massive case of stage fright. Then, when it&amp;rsquo;s announced that an asteroid may be heading cataclysmically towards the Earth, all social order breaks down and the honest and honorable life takes a backseat to a frenzied, panicked mayhem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Island Song</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/island-song/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/island-song/</guid>
      <description>The rush of the city keeps rhythmic time, and five young people traveling down uncertain paths are caught up in the pulse of life in New York. This cutting-edge new musical from the acclaimed songwriting duo, Carner and Gregor, examines the struggle of finding love, the struggle of finding success, and, above all, the struggle of finding yourself in a big city where everyone seems somehow interconnected. Produced in partnership with Indiana University Theatre &amp;amp; Drama, this innovative musical takes shape in a full production after its workshop on IU&amp;rsquo;s campus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Banana Tree</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/the-banana-tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2013 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/the-banana-tree/</guid>
      <description>From the minds of The Simpsons stars, Dan Castellaneta (Homer Simpson) and Deb Lacusta (writer), comes a zany comedy about Angela, a convenience store clerk who dreams of being Las Vegas&amp;rsquo; first African American female magician. But after a series of hilarious run-ins and blunders, Angela finds herself in the middle of a robbery, a kidnapping, and at the mercy of a criminal mastermind that also happens to be a telepathic banana tree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sequence</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/sequence/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/sequence/</guid>
      <description>In this edge-of-your-seat science thriller, two intertwined stories teem with coincidence. In one, Time Magazine&amp;rsquo;s Luckiest Man Alive has correctly bet on the Super Bowl coin toss 19 years in a row. He is about to risk $880 million on the 20th until he&amp;rsquo;s confronted by a young woman who may be able to prove that mathematics is behind his &amp;ldquo;luck.&amp;rdquo; In the other, an extremely unlucky man improbably guesses wrong on all 150 multiple choice questions of his science exam, which he feels is a sign from a higher power.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spun</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2012-2013/spun/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2013 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2012-2013/spun/</guid>
      <description>Following their father&amp;rsquo;s death, Molly and her estranged brother Jesse try to find a way to reconnect within the ruins of their childhood. But memories have a funny way of changing over time; and with two very different recollections blame, doubt, and rock &amp;lsquo;n&amp;rsquo; roll become weapons. The composer and lyricist of the hit Kissing Frogs, Jeremy Schonfeld returns to create this high-octane musical that explores the complexities of family and story-telling, weaving together the memories and unique perspectives of siblings with comedy, wit, and rock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ampersand</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2012-2013/ampersand/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2013 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2012-2013/ampersand/</guid>
      <description>Things aren&amp;rsquo;t working out for Kate and Marlowe. He&amp;rsquo;s an unemployed whiner, and despite her best efforts to stick with him, Kate just couldn&amp;rsquo;t help cloning him. Twice. When one of the clones slips into Marlowe&amp;rsquo;s life, and Kate discovers that she might not actually be the original Kate, things get scarier and funnier at the same time. Just what is marriage? And how far will we go to change each other—and ourselves—to stay together?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Truman Show</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2012-2013/the-truman-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2012-2013/the-truman-show/</guid>
      <description>Based on the original film by Andrew Niccol
Based on the beloved 1998 film, this musical follows Truman, an ordinary man unaware he&amp;rsquo;s being watched by millions from all over the world. He lives in a large studio with hidden cameras everywhere. All his friends and townspeople are actors playing their roles in the most popular TV-series in the world: &amp;ldquo;The Truman Show&amp;rdquo;. When an actress falls in love with him, she breaks onto the set to tell him the truth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lemonade</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2012-2013/lemonade/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2012 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2012-2013/lemonade/</guid>
      <description>Ever hear the one about the unsuccessful comedian and his garbage sculpting wife? They strive for the American dream while struggling to pay their bills, escape eviction and cope with friends who increasingly seem like strangers. Life, they tell their kids, is sort of like Dad&amp;rsquo;s monologues: no matter how fearlessly you struggle you&amp;rsquo;re only as good as your punch line.
Lemonade was chosen as the best out of 450 submissions from around the world as part of its Woodward/Newman Drama Competition, named after two of the greatest actors of our time, Joanne Woodward &amp;amp; Paul Newman and sponsored by Newman&amp;rsquo;s Own Foundation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rx</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2012-2013/rx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2012-2013/rx/</guid>
      <description>Meena Pierotti&amp;rsquo;s job is making her unhappy. Luckily, there&amp;rsquo;s a pill for that. Well, not yet. But Meena has joined the clinical trial for a new drug targeting workplace depression. The trial gets messy, however, when her doctor falls in love with her, and he chooses to enroll himself in a drug trial targeting heartbreak.
The BPP&amp;rsquo;s Off-Broadway/On-9th series seeks to take a play recently seen at a small theatre in NYC and help it to have a future life across the country by producing it here at the BPP at 9th Street.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2011 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/about/</guid>
      <description>The Bloomington Playwrights Project (BPP) is the only professional theatre in the entire state of Indiana dedicated solely to new plays. In operation for 40 years, we serve both the Bloomington and national theatre community by working with talented playwrights, actors, and artists to develop high-level productions for our local patrons as well as the many audiences attending subsequent productions of scripts that originated here at the BPP. We are an advocate for playwrights and new plays and believe firmly that they are not only important but absolutely vital to the future of our art form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Redirecting you...</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/program/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2011 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/program/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Season at a Glance</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/season/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2011 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/season/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annual Gala</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2017-2018/annual-gala/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2017-2018/annual-gala/</guid>
      <description>Hosted by Marc Summers, the BPP Annual Gala will be a lively, classy evening! The theme is Game Night so bring your competitive spirit! Cocktail hour will take place in three different areas from 6:30pm – 7:30pm, with exciting games throughout. You’ll be able to mingle, bid on silent auction items, and check out the delicious appetizers and beverages!
The main event takes place in the auditorium from 7:30pm – 10:00pm and will include the live auction and an amazing dinner from IMU Catering.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>