<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>and Starring Baba Brinkman on Bloomington Playwrights Project</title>
    <link>http://newplays.org/playwrights/and-starring-baba-brinkman/</link>
    <description>Recent content in and Starring Baba Brinkman on Bloomington Playwrights Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2019 19:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://newplays.org/playwrights/and-starring-baba-brinkman/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Rap Guide to Consciousness</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/rap-guide-to-conciousnes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/rap-guide-to-conciousnes/</guid>
      <description>PLEASE BE AWARE: Rap Guide to Consciousness and Rap Guide to Culture are SOLD SEPERATLY.
“Peer reviewed rapper” Baba Brinkman takes a deep dive into the neuroscience of human experience, from sensations to hallucinations. “Mind-blowingly, awe-inspiringly good”. (Broadway Baby) Baba’s brain consists of tens of billions of neurons, none of which has any idea that he exists. And yet, somehow, those cells come together to produce a steady stream of ill rhymes, laughs, and revelations about the mind we live in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rap Guide to Culture</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/rap-guide-to-culture/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2019 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/rap-guide-to-culture/</guid>
      <description>PLEASE BE AWARE: Rap Guide to Consciousness and Rap Guide to Culture are SOLD SEPERATLY.
Music, poetry, art, science, politics, and relationships are all strange behaviors found in a species of (mostly) hairless primates. How do norms and social systems evolve, and who benefits? The whole planet hangs in the balance as cultures and sub-cultures compete for survival and the reach to become viral. Equal parts rap concert, TED Talk, and stand-up gig, Rap Guide to Culture surprises, delights, and ultimately heals, bringing a wealth of knowledge and razor-sharp observational wit to some of today’s stickiest topics.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>