<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2017-2018 on Bloomington Playwrights Project</title>
    <link>http://newplays.org/series/2017-2018/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2017-2018 on Bloomington Playwrights Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 18:30:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://newplays.org/series/2017-2018/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Vintage Songs</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2017-2018/vintage-songs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 18:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2017-2018/vintage-songs/</guid>
      <description>This June, we invite you to expand your dramatic palate with an all-new show featuring a performance of favorite songs from BPP&amp;rsquo;s original musicals, as well as the announcement of the 2018-19 Season. The evening begins Thursday, June 14, 2018 with a full buffet dinner at 6:30pm, followed by the performances at 7:30pm. A cash bar with wine will also be open. This year we’ll be at the Oliver Winery Creekbend Vineyard at 7508 N Woodall Road, in Ellettsville.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Oregon Trail</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/the-oregon-trail/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/the-oregon-trail/</guid>
      <description>13 year-old Jane has always had trouble making choices. Looking for an escape, she seeks refuge in the classic ‘80s video game, “The Oregon Trail” — where the choices are clear, the results are sure, and there’s always another life to live (after everyone dies of dysentery). But as time blurs, the boundaries between game and reality become hazy, until Jane finds herself leaping headfirst into the world of The Oregon Trail, where she’s forced to confront the choices she’s made, connect with her family, keep her oxen safe, and ford the river of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out of Orbit</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/out-of-orbit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/out-of-orbit/</guid>
      <description>Sara, one of the world’s most brilliant planetary geologists, lives her life on Mars time — her days lasting longer and longer as she monitors mankind’s latest voyage to the Red Planet. But her daughter, Lis, continues to live her life as a teenager on Earth time, showing no interest in her mother’s world out in space—despite Sara’s best efforts. As both of their lives begin to spin out of control, they must grapple with the distance their two time zones create between them… even when they’re standing side by side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spun: A Brother/Sister Rock Musical</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/spun/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/spun/</guid>
      <description>Back by popular demand, one of BPP’s most beloved musicals returns with 6 new songs and some new surprises in store. Don’t miss this encore performance as it prepares for an anticipated NYC run!
Following their father’s death, Molly and her estranged brother Jesse come home to pick up the pieces. But as they begin to recount their childhood together, two very different stories are revealed… and rock-n-roll tears through the past to uncover wounds that still must be healed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Front Page Flo</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/front-page-flo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/front-page-flo/</guid>
      <description>In post-WWII New York City, the newspaper is king, and rambunctious reporter Flo is hungry for her big break. So when word hits the wires that a Soviet spy has landed in Manhattan, Flo follows the clues to get the scoop — and discovers more than she bargained for. With a golden-era Broadway score, dazzling dance numbers, loves lost (and found again), and non-stop fun, FRONT PAGE FLO is the world premiere musical that feels like seeing a classic for the very first time!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ike &amp; Julie Arnove Playoffs</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2017-2018/ike-and-julie-arnove-playoffs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2017 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2017-2018/ike-and-julie-arnove-playoffs/</guid>
      <description>Donate to the 2017 Ike &amp;amp; Julie Arnove PlayOffs!
It’s that time of the year again for the Ike &amp;amp; Julie Arnove PlayOffs. The time of year when we separate the contenders from the pretenders, the pros from the joes, the heroes from the zeros. Yes, that’s right, the baseball playoffs are just around the corner. In celebration, the BPP is presenting its most electrifying, action-packed, and anticipated fundraising event of the year, the Ike &amp;amp; Julie Arnove PlayOffs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beating A Dead Horse</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/beating-a-dead-horse/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/beating-a-dead-horse/</guid>
      <description>Brothers Steve and Marty Martin are on the brink of closing their failing pet funeral home, until an eccentric (and rich) new customer comes in with an amazing proposition: plan a funeral for her nearly dead racehorse, and she’ll give the boys a fortune to keep their business afloat. The only problem? The horse won’t die. With everything on the line, the two embark on a hysterical journey to see how far they’ll go to make their dreams come true, in this laugh-a-minute screwball comedy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annual Gala</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2017-2018/annual-gala/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2017-2018/annual-gala/</guid>
      <description>Hosted by Marc Summers, the BPP Annual Gala will be a lively, classy evening! The theme is Game Night so bring your competitive spirit! Cocktail hour will take place in three different areas from 6:30pm – 7:30pm, with exciting games throughout. You’ll be able to mingle, bid on silent auction items, and check out the delicious appetizers and beverages!
The main event takes place in the auditorium from 7:30pm – 10:00pm and will include the live auction and an amazing dinner from IMU Catering.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>