<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shows on Bloomington Playwrights Project</title>
    <link>http://newplays.org/show/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Shows on Bloomington Playwrights Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 19:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://newplays.org/show/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Burdens</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/the-burdens/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/the-burdens/</guid>
      <description>Siblings Mordy and Jane communicate like proper millennials: primarily through text message and loaded with sarcasm. When their loving mother’s life becomes emotionally and financially taxed by their absolutely awful and 100-year-old grandfather, Zad-Zad, they draw together an elaborate plot to…relieve their mother’s burden. Told almost entirely via text messages, The Burdens is a dark, family comedy about how technology helps keep us close, while still enabling us to keep our distance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Absentee</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/the-absentee/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/the-absentee/</guid>
      <description>Far out in the Milky Way, “Beacons” serve as lighthouses for warping spaceships around the galaxy. When a U.S. Space Forces ship explodes near Beacon 44.AR.90, its Operator finds herself alone in deep space with only her ship’s AI for companionship. That is, until a persistent canvasser calls, desperate to convince her to vote absentee in the 2088 election.
Box office opens at 6:30pm, house opens at 7pm, shows begin at 7:30pm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Enlightenment of Percival Von Schmootz</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/percival-von-schmootz/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/percival-von-schmootz/</guid>
      <description>Fed up with a world filled with plagues, pestilence, and poor personal hygiene, a ridiculously optimistic young man sets out on a quest to end the Dark Ages. As he attempts to bring the light of hope to the world, Percival Von Schmootz meets with hilariously disastrous results at every turn. Yet in this outrageous, Monty Python-esque musical comedy, it is only when things look the darkest that Percival is able to discover what true enlightenment means, as he finds hope (and humor) in impossibly bleak circumstances.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lost Letters</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/lost-letters/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/lost-letters/</guid>
      <description>Newly married, newly moved, and with a newborn on the way, Adam is scrambling to get everything ready for the arrival of his daughter – all the while questioning the choices that brought him to this moment. While clearing out boxes from his soon-to-be nursery, he finds a trove of handwritten letters from his past. The letters come to life and force Adam to (finally) reply, make peace with the present, and embrace his new reality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rap Guide to Consciousness</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/rap-guide-to-conciousnes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/rap-guide-to-conciousnes/</guid>
      <description>PLEASE BE AWARE: Rap Guide to Consciousness and Rap Guide to Culture are SOLD SEPERATLY.
“Peer reviewed rapper” Baba Brinkman takes a deep dive into the neuroscience of human experience, from sensations to hallucinations. “Mind-blowingly, awe-inspiringly good”. (Broadway Baby) Baba’s brain consists of tens of billions of neurons, none of which has any idea that he exists. And yet, somehow, those cells come together to produce a steady stream of ill rhymes, laughs, and revelations about the mind we live in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rap Guide to Culture</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/rap-guide-to-culture/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2019 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/rap-guide-to-culture/</guid>
      <description>PLEASE BE AWARE: Rap Guide to Consciousness and Rap Guide to Culture are SOLD SEPERATLY.
Music, poetry, art, science, politics, and relationships are all strange behaviors found in a species of (mostly) hairless primates. How do norms and social systems evolve, and who benefits? The whole planet hangs in the balance as cultures and sub-cultures compete for survival and the reach to become viral. Equal parts rap concert, TED Talk, and stand-up gig, Rap Guide to Culture surprises, delights, and ultimately heals, bringing a wealth of knowledge and razor-sharp observational wit to some of today’s stickiest topics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To Quiet the Quiet</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2018-2019/to-quiet-the-quiet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2018-2019/to-quiet-the-quiet/</guid>
      <description>From the writer of the hit musical Home.
Having suffered great loss and heartbreak, Kathy is a woman on the edge. Haunted by her past and her own personal demons, Kathy seems to be losing the battle against her thoughts, her words, and her fears. And the one man who can help her may prove to be just as powerless against her…
Contains violence and may not be suitable for all ages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Jedi Handbook</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2018-2019/the-jedi-handbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2018-2019/the-jedi-handbook/</guid>
      <description>A not so long time ago, in a theater not so far away, came a film that rocked the galaxy – changing both cinema and schoolyards forever…
The Jedi Handbook is a coming of age story about a young boy who survives growing older with help from The Force. Experiencing the Star Wars franchise anew, through the eyes and imagination of a kid, The Jedi Handbook takes us on a nostalgic journey back to an era we can all relate to – our childhood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apropos of Nothing</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2018-2019/apropos-of-nothing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2018-2019/apropos-of-nothing/</guid>
      <description>Owen confesses, apropos of nothing, that he’s in love with his best friend’s wife.
But it’s just “a passing phase,” he tells him. “Forget I even said it.” Unfortunately, no one can. And now that it’s out there, everyone’s lives are turned upside-down, and no one’s relationship is safe from the wreckage. In a comedy about love, irony, and cliché, five people struggle with…well…love, irony, and cliché.
Contains adult language and situations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tuning In</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2018-2019/tuning-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2018-2019/tuning-in/</guid>
      <description>All is peaceful at the Harmony Hill retirement community – the rooms are comfy, the meals are tasty, and the citizen-run radio station is a hit (even if it only plays hits from the past). But when an executive waltzes in threatening to take over WLK 89.3 and turn it into a contemporary music station, the talented tenants of the senior center band together and hold a radiothon to keep it alive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glitches in Reality</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2018-2019/glitches-in-reality/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2018-2019/glitches-in-reality/</guid>
      <description>From the mind of renowned Australian magician, Simon Coronel, comes an evening filled with astonishing and impossible events. Glitches in Reality uses close-up trickery and mind-blowing sleight of hand to take the audience on a journey through the truth behind magic and illusion; a truth that is far more amazing than even the illusions themselves.
Winner of over a dozen international awards including multiple from the prestigious World Championships of Magic, Simon is a regular performer at the Magic Castle and is a university lecturer on perception and illusion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Oregon Trail</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/the-oregon-trail/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/the-oregon-trail/</guid>
      <description>13 year-old Jane has always had trouble making choices. Looking for an escape, she seeks refuge in the classic ‘80s video game, “The Oregon Trail” — where the choices are clear, the results are sure, and there’s always another life to live (after everyone dies of dysentery). But as time blurs, the boundaries between game and reality become hazy, until Jane finds herself leaping headfirst into the world of The Oregon Trail, where she’s forced to confront the choices she’s made, connect with her family, keep her oxen safe, and ford the river of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out of Orbit</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/out-of-orbit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/out-of-orbit/</guid>
      <description>Sara, one of the world’s most brilliant planetary geologists, lives her life on Mars time — her days lasting longer and longer as she monitors mankind’s latest voyage to the Red Planet. But her daughter, Lis, continues to live her life as a teenager on Earth time, showing no interest in her mother’s world out in space—despite Sara’s best efforts. As both of their lives begin to spin out of control, they must grapple with the distance their two time zones create between them… even when they’re standing side by side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spun: A Brother/Sister Rock Musical</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/spun/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/spun/</guid>
      <description>Back by popular demand, one of BPP’s most beloved musicals returns with 6 new songs and some new surprises in store. Don’t miss this encore performance as it prepares for an anticipated NYC run!
Following their father’s death, Molly and her estranged brother Jesse come home to pick up the pieces. But as they begin to recount their childhood together, two very different stories are revealed… and rock-n-roll tears through the past to uncover wounds that still must be healed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Front Page Flo</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/front-page-flo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/front-page-flo/</guid>
      <description>In post-WWII New York City, the newspaper is king, and rambunctious reporter Flo is hungry for her big break. So when word hits the wires that a Soviet spy has landed in Manhattan, Flo follows the clues to get the scoop — and discovers more than she bargained for. With a golden-era Broadway score, dazzling dance numbers, loves lost (and found again), and non-stop fun, FRONT PAGE FLO is the world premiere musical that feels like seeing a classic for the very first time!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beating A Dead Horse</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/beating-a-dead-horse/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/beating-a-dead-horse/</guid>
      <description>Brothers Steve and Marty Martin are on the brink of closing their failing pet funeral home, until an eccentric (and rich) new customer comes in with an amazing proposition: plan a funeral for her nearly dead racehorse, and she’ll give the boys a fortune to keep their business afloat. The only problem? The horse won’t die. With everything on the line, the two embark on a hysterical journey to see how far they’ll go to make their dreams come true, in this laugh-a-minute screwball comedy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happily After Ever</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/happily-after-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/happily-after-ever/</guid>
      <description>Newlyweds Darren and Janet want nothing more than to build the perfect life together. But when Janet gives birth to a baby with both male and female genitalia, they find themselves in the unlikely position of having to choose a gender for their child - all while competing with the perfect couple next door and dealing with a misunderstood family dog - in this hilarious battle of the sexes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calling All Kates</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/calling-all-kates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2017 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/calling-all-kates/</guid>
      <description>Marc gets dumped by his fiancé, Kate McBride, right before their wedding and honeymoon around the world. He’s now single and left to travel the globe alone since his plane tickets are non-transferrable and non-refundable. In an act of desperation, Marc posts an ad online for the only companion who could legally join him&amp;hellip; someone with the exact same name as his ex-fiancé. Set loose in a bunch of different foreign countries, strangers Marc and Kate must get to know one another and learn to get along in the wake of Marc&amp;rsquo;s heartbreak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Row After Row</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/row-after-row/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/row-after-row/</guid>
      <description>Historical accuracy is paramount to Cal and Tom, two hardcore Civil War re-enactors, fresh off their latest Gettysburg battle. But their accuracy is compromised when they’re joined by a soldier with a less than authentic confederate uniform&amp;hellip; and the wrong gender. Straddling 1863 and today, ROW AFTER ROW is a dark comedy about choosing your cause and finding your courage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/home/</guid>
      <description>Katherine escaped from her small Texas home and her hypochondriac mother 9 years ago. When she finally steps back into her childhood home, Katherine is immediately overwhelmed by the familiar. Every room seems to have a story. Every corner of the house holds another recollection. Katherine’s memories become so vivid, in fact, they appear to come alive before her eyes. Both humorous and heartbreaking, HOME explores parenting and childhood with unflinching honesty, questioning what it means to grow older, and whether we truly have the capacity to grow up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Day Mourning Period</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/30-day-mourning-period/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/30-day-mourning-period/</guid>
      <description>Larry, Susan and Craig are locked in mind-numbing sales jobs that are slowly draining each of them. But everything changes when their boss, Mr. Clybourne, kills himself one morning, and their company grants the office a 30-day &amp;ldquo;mourning period&amp;rdquo; with no sales goals, no dress codes and no corporate oversight. With a newfound freedom and an unbridled sense of adventure, the three thrust themselves into their own tale of rebellion, and over the course of their mourning period they build a castle out of office supplies, encounter an army of rats, fight with water balloons, drink excessive amounts of tequila, discover meaning in their previously meaningless monotony and ultimately attempt to right the wrongs of their company’s impersonal policies in their own makeshift revolution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Capables</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/the-capables/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/the-capables/</guid>
      <description>Anna Capable is a hoarder. The stacks of McDonald&amp;rsquo;s happy meal toys, beanie babies, and useless junk pile straight up to the ceiling, forcing her daughter, Jessy, to call a TV network in hopes of clearing the mess and curing her mother. But the TV network&amp;rsquo;s producer, David, is looking for more than just another cluttered home to get the ratings he needs. With his career on the line, he&amp;rsquo;s hungry to expose the Capables&amp;rsquo; dirty laundry &amp;ndash; whether it&amp;rsquo;s in their house, or their personal lives &amp;ndash; at all costs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ugly Lies the Bone</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/ugly-lies-the-bone/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/ugly-lies-the-bone/</guid>
      <description>Female soldier, Jess, returns from war severely burned only to find her Floridian hometown decaying with the end of the space shuttle era. She moves in with her sister and struggles through immense pain to define a new sense of &amp;ldquo;normal&amp;rdquo; when all she wants is her old life back. Using virtual reality therapy, Jess builds a dream world of cooling snow to calm her mind as she desperately tries to restore her relationships, home, and all that was lost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Me Bad</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/make-me-bad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2015 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/make-me-bad/</guid>
      <description>by special arrangement with The Benge Group
What happens when you fall in love with a serial killer? This gritty and sexy musical thriller follows the story of Daisy Harris, a young woman stuck in a small town with a dead-end job, an overbearing mother, and a troubled past. Desperate to escape but with nowhere to go, Daisy looks for anything to break the monotony of her meaningless life. She meets charming and cryptic Max, just as a string of unexplained murders rocks the town.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>She Kills Monsters</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/she-kills-monsters/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2014 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/she-kills-monsters/</guid>
      <description>Agnes never paid much attention to her teenage sister, Tilly, who took refuge in the role-playing world. But when a tragedy strikes and Tilly is lost forever, Agnes goes searching in the one place she can still be found: her late sister&amp;rsquo;s Dungeons &amp;amp; Dragons notebook. With the help of the game store clerk, Chuck, Agnes dives into the fantastical world of fairies, ogres, dragons, and even blood thirsty cheerleaders, in an action-packed comedy that searches for the warrior&amp;hellip; and the geek&amp;hellip; within us all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kalamazoo</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/kalamazoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2014 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/kalamazoo/</guid>
      <description>When Peg, a 70-something, Irish Catholic bird lover meets Irving, a 70-something Jewish, metal detector-toting East Coaster on an online dating site, it feels like love at first click. But after their crazy margarita-filled first date, complete with body shots and morning-after tattoos, Peg and Irving find that they still have a little aging to do if they want to forget their past and move forward into a future together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greta</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/greta/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/greta/</guid>
      <description>In the exciting next phase of its evolution, Kissing Frogs, one of BPP&amp;rsquo;s best-selling shows ever, returns for its second draft with some new songs and an all-new story. It all happened at the Stop Drop &amp;amp; Bowl. At least that&amp;rsquo;s how Greta&amp;rsquo;s beginning to feel about every major event in her life. After college, Greta puts her future on hold to help her grandmother run the family bowling alley, the very same one she grew up in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mad Gravity</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/mad-gravity/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2014 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/mad-gravity/</guid>
      <description>Archie and Eudora have built a live studio audience in their living room. Being constantly observed helps them to lead an honest and honorable life. But things get awkward when some important visitors get a massive case of stage fright. Then, when it&amp;rsquo;s announced that an asteroid may be heading cataclysmically towards the Earth, all social order breaks down and the honest and honorable life takes a backseat to a frenzied, panicked mayhem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Island Song</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/island-song/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/island-song/</guid>
      <description>The rush of the city keeps rhythmic time, and five young people traveling down uncertain paths are caught up in the pulse of life in New York. This cutting-edge new musical from the acclaimed songwriting duo, Carner and Gregor, examines the struggle of finding love, the struggle of finding success, and, above all, the struggle of finding yourself in a big city where everyone seems somehow interconnected. Produced in partnership with Indiana University Theatre &amp;amp; Drama, this innovative musical takes shape in a full production after its workshop on IU&amp;rsquo;s campus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Banana Tree</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/the-banana-tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2013 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/the-banana-tree/</guid>
      <description>From the minds of The Simpsons stars, Dan Castellaneta (Homer Simpson) and Deb Lacusta (writer), comes a zany comedy about Angela, a convenience store clerk who dreams of being Las Vegas&amp;rsquo; first African American female magician. But after a series of hilarious run-ins and blunders, Angela finds herself in the middle of a robbery, a kidnapping, and at the mercy of a criminal mastermind that also happens to be a telepathic banana tree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sequence</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/sequence/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/sequence/</guid>
      <description>In this edge-of-your-seat science thriller, two intertwined stories teem with coincidence. In one, Time Magazine&amp;rsquo;s Luckiest Man Alive has correctly bet on the Super Bowl coin toss 19 years in a row. He is about to risk $880 million on the 20th until he&amp;rsquo;s confronted by a young woman who may be able to prove that mathematics is behind his &amp;ldquo;luck.&amp;rdquo; In the other, an extremely unlucky man improbably guesses wrong on all 150 multiple choice questions of his science exam, which he feels is a sign from a higher power.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spun</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2012-2013/spun/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2013 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2012-2013/spun/</guid>
      <description>Following their father&amp;rsquo;s death, Molly and her estranged brother Jesse try to find a way to reconnect within the ruins of their childhood. But memories have a funny way of changing over time; and with two very different recollections blame, doubt, and rock &amp;lsquo;n&amp;rsquo; roll become weapons. The composer and lyricist of the hit Kissing Frogs, Jeremy Schonfeld returns to create this high-octane musical that explores the complexities of family and story-telling, weaving together the memories and unique perspectives of siblings with comedy, wit, and rock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ampersand</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2012-2013/ampersand/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2013 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2012-2013/ampersand/</guid>
      <description>Things aren&amp;rsquo;t working out for Kate and Marlowe. He&amp;rsquo;s an unemployed whiner, and despite her best efforts to stick with him, Kate just couldn&amp;rsquo;t help cloning him. Twice. When one of the clones slips into Marlowe&amp;rsquo;s life, and Kate discovers that she might not actually be the original Kate, things get scarier and funnier at the same time. Just what is marriage? And how far will we go to change each other—and ourselves—to stay together?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Truman Show</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2012-2013/the-truman-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2012-2013/the-truman-show/</guid>
      <description>Based on the original film by Andrew Niccol
Based on the beloved 1998 film, this musical follows Truman, an ordinary man unaware he&amp;rsquo;s being watched by millions from all over the world. He lives in a large studio with hidden cameras everywhere. All his friends and townspeople are actors playing their roles in the most popular TV-series in the world: &amp;ldquo;The Truman Show&amp;rdquo;. When an actress falls in love with him, she breaks onto the set to tell him the truth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lemonade</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2012-2013/lemonade/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2012 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2012-2013/lemonade/</guid>
      <description>Ever hear the one about the unsuccessful comedian and his garbage sculpting wife? They strive for the American dream while struggling to pay their bills, escape eviction and cope with friends who increasingly seem like strangers. Life, they tell their kids, is sort of like Dad&amp;rsquo;s monologues: no matter how fearlessly you struggle you&amp;rsquo;re only as good as your punch line.
Lemonade was chosen as the best out of 450 submissions from around the world as part of its Woodward/Newman Drama Competition, named after two of the greatest actors of our time, Joanne Woodward &amp;amp; Paul Newman and sponsored by Newman&amp;rsquo;s Own Foundation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rx</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2012-2013/rx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2012-2013/rx/</guid>
      <description>Meena Pierotti&amp;rsquo;s job is making her unhappy. Luckily, there&amp;rsquo;s a pill for that. Well, not yet. But Meena has joined the clinical trial for a new drug targeting workplace depression. The trial gets messy, however, when her doctor falls in love with her, and he chooses to enroll himself in a drug trial targeting heartbreak.
The BPP&amp;rsquo;s Off-Broadway/On-9th series seeks to take a play recently seen at a small theatre in NYC and help it to have a future life across the country by producing it here at the BPP at 9th Street.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>