<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2018-2019 on Bloomington Playwrights Project</title>
    <link>http://newplays.org/series/2018-2019/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2018-2019 on Bloomington Playwrights Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 18:30:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://newplays.org/series/2018-2019/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>BPP&#39;s 40th Birthday Celebration</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/vintage-songs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 18:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/vintage-songs/</guid>
      <description>This June 6th, we are throwing ourselves a 40th Birthday Celebration! Start the night out at 6:30 with donated food, wine, and beer! Then move into the theatre for the announcement of our 2019-2020 Season and a staged read of the 2014 SMASH HIT Kalamazoo. Join the original cast and relive the wonderful story of BPP&amp;rsquo;s best selling show of all time. Then stick around for the announcement of the 2019-20 Season (our 40th!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To Quiet the Quiet</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2018-2019/to-quiet-the-quiet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2018-2019/to-quiet-the-quiet/</guid>
      <description>From the writer of the hit musical Home.
Having suffered great loss and heartbreak, Kathy is a woman on the edge. Haunted by her past and her own personal demons, Kathy seems to be losing the battle against her thoughts, her words, and her fears. And the one man who can help her may prove to be just as powerless against her…
Contains violence and may not be suitable for all ages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Jedi Handbook</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2018-2019/the-jedi-handbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2018-2019/the-jedi-handbook/</guid>
      <description>A not so long time ago, in a theater not so far away, came a film that rocked the galaxy – changing both cinema and schoolyards forever…
The Jedi Handbook is a coming of age story about a young boy who survives growing older with help from The Force. Experiencing the Star Wars franchise anew, through the eyes and imagination of a kid, The Jedi Handbook takes us on a nostalgic journey back to an era we can all relate to – our childhood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apropos of Nothing</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2018-2019/apropos-of-nothing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2018-2019/apropos-of-nothing/</guid>
      <description>Owen confesses, apropos of nothing, that he’s in love with his best friend’s wife.
But it’s just “a passing phase,” he tells him. “Forget I even said it.” Unfortunately, no one can. And now that it’s out there, everyone’s lives are turned upside-down, and no one’s relationship is safe from the wreckage. In a comedy about love, irony, and cliché, five people struggle with…well…love, irony, and cliché.
Contains adult language and situations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Days of Dinner</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/30-days-of-dinners/</guid>
      <description>BPP&amp;rsquo;S ONLINE AUCTION is here! http://tinyurl.com/bppauction and take a look at all our fabulous items!
You are invited to BPP&amp;rsquo;s 30 Days of Dinner, a brand new special event taking the place of our annual gala. 30 Days of Dinner is unlike any of the other events. It happens over the entire month of January instead of one single day, so you can find the day that works best for you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tuning In</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2018-2019/tuning-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2018-2019/tuning-in/</guid>
      <description>All is peaceful at the Harmony Hill retirement community – the rooms are comfy, the meals are tasty, and the citizen-run radio station is a hit (even if it only plays hits from the past). But when an executive waltzes in threatening to take over WLK 89.3 and turn it into a contemporary music station, the talented tenants of the senior center band together and hold a radiothon to keep it alive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ike &amp; Julie Arnove PlayOffs</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/ike-and-julie-arnove-playoffs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/ike-and-julie-arnove-playoffs/</guid>
      <description>Batter up for the Ike &amp;amp; Julie Arnove PlayOffs! It&amp;rsquo;s almost that time of year again when we separate the contenders from the pretenders, the pros from the joes, the heroes from the zeros. Yes, that’s right - the baseball playoffs are just around the corner. In celebration, the BPP is presenting its most electrifying, action-packed, and anticipated fundraising event of the year, the Ike &amp;amp; Julie Arnove PlayOffs!
Just what are The PlayOffs, you ask?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glitches in Reality</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2018-2019/glitches-in-reality/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2018-2019/glitches-in-reality/</guid>
      <description>From the mind of renowned Australian magician, Simon Coronel, comes an evening filled with astonishing and impossible events. Glitches in Reality uses close-up trickery and mind-blowing sleight of hand to take the audience on a journey through the truth behind magic and illusion; a truth that is far more amazing than even the illusions themselves.
Winner of over a dozen international awards including multiple from the prestigious World Championships of Magic, Simon is a regular performer at the Magic Castle and is a university lecturer on perception and illusion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Your Marc</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/on-your-marc-screening/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/on-your-marc-screening/</guid>
      <description>Do you remember back in 2016 when beloved TV icon, Marc Summers, premiered his one-man show Everything in Its Place: The Life and Slimes of Marc Summers at BPP? We sure do. Well, while that was going on, a documentary crew was filming.
Fast forward 2 years&amp;hellip; Surprise! Marc is joining us again this fall for a sneak preview screening of the completed film! On Your Marc intimately captures his life, career, and legacy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>