<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>David Anspaugh on Bloomington Playwrights Project</title>
    <link>http://newplays.org/directors/david-anspaugh/</link>
    <description>Recent content in David Anspaugh on Bloomington Playwrights Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 19:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://newplays.org/directors/david-anspaugh/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>To Quiet the Quiet</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2018-2019/to-quiet-the-quiet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2018-2019/to-quiet-the-quiet/</guid>
      <description>From the writer of the hit musical Home.
Having suffered great loss and heartbreak, Kathy is a woman on the edge. Haunted by her past and her own personal demons, Kathy seems to be losing the battle against her thoughts, her words, and her fears. And the one man who can help her may prove to be just as powerless against her…
Contains violence and may not be suitable for all ages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Row After Row</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/row-after-row/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/row-after-row/</guid>
      <description>Historical accuracy is paramount to Cal and Tom, two hardcore Civil War re-enactors, fresh off their latest Gettysburg battle. But their accuracy is compromised when they’re joined by a soldier with a less than authentic confederate uniform&amp;hellip; and the wrong gender. Straddling 1863 and today, ROW AFTER ROW is a dark comedy about choosing your cause and finding your courage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ugly Lies the Bone</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/ugly-lies-the-bone/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/ugly-lies-the-bone/</guid>
      <description>Female soldier, Jess, returns from war severely burned only to find her Floridian hometown decaying with the end of the space shuttle era. She moves in with her sister and struggles through immense pain to define a new sense of &amp;ldquo;normal&amp;rdquo; when all she wants is her old life back. Using virtual reality therapy, Jess builds a dream world of cooling snow to calm her mind as she desperately tries to restore her relationships, home, and all that was lost.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>