<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>musical on Bloomington Playwrights Project</title>
    <link>http://newplays.org/genres/musical/</link>
    <description>Recent content in musical on Bloomington Playwrights Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 19:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://newplays.org/genres/musical/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Enlightenment of Percival Von Schmootz</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/percival-von-schmootz/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/percival-von-schmootz/</guid>
      <description>Fed up with a world filled with plagues, pestilence, and poor personal hygiene, a ridiculously optimistic young man sets out on a quest to end the Dark Ages. As he attempts to bring the light of hope to the world, Percival Von Schmootz meets with hilariously disastrous results at every turn. Yet in this outrageous, Monty Python-esque musical comedy, it is only when things look the darkest that Percival is able to discover what true enlightenment means, as he finds hope (and humor) in impossibly bleak circumstances.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lost Letters</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/lost-letters/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/lost-letters/</guid>
      <description>Newly married, newly moved, and with a newborn on the way, Adam is scrambling to get everything ready for the arrival of his daughter – all the while questioning the choices that brought him to this moment. While clearing out boxes from his soon-to-be nursery, he finds a trove of handwritten letters from his past. The letters come to life and force Adam to (finally) reply, make peace with the present, and embrace his new reality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tuning In</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2018-2019/tuning-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2018-2019/tuning-in/</guid>
      <description>All is peaceful at the Harmony Hill retirement community – the rooms are comfy, the meals are tasty, and the citizen-run radio station is a hit (even if it only plays hits from the past). But when an executive waltzes in threatening to take over WLK 89.3 and turn it into a contemporary music station, the talented tenants of the senior center band together and hold a radiothon to keep it alive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spun: A Brother/Sister Rock Musical</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/spun/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/spun/</guid>
      <description>Back by popular demand, one of BPP’s most beloved musicals returns with 6 new songs and some new surprises in store. Don’t miss this encore performance as it prepares for an anticipated NYC run!
Following their father’s death, Molly and her estranged brother Jesse come home to pick up the pieces. But as they begin to recount their childhood together, two very different stories are revealed… and rock-n-roll tears through the past to uncover wounds that still must be healed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Front Page Flo</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/front-page-flo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/front-page-flo/</guid>
      <description>In post-WWII New York City, the newspaper is king, and rambunctious reporter Flo is hungry for her big break. So when word hits the wires that a Soviet spy has landed in Manhattan, Flo follows the clues to get the scoop — and discovers more than she bargained for. With a golden-era Broadway score, dazzling dance numbers, loves lost (and found again), and non-stop fun, FRONT PAGE FLO is the world premiere musical that feels like seeing a classic for the very first time!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calling All Kates</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/calling-all-kates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2017 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/calling-all-kates/</guid>
      <description>Marc gets dumped by his fiancé, Kate McBride, right before their wedding and honeymoon around the world. He’s now single and left to travel the globe alone since his plane tickets are non-transferrable and non-refundable. In an act of desperation, Marc posts an ad online for the only companion who could legally join him&amp;hellip; someone with the exact same name as his ex-fiancé. Set loose in a bunch of different foreign countries, strangers Marc and Kate must get to know one another and learn to get along in the wake of Marc&amp;rsquo;s heartbreak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/home/</guid>
      <description>Katherine escaped from her small Texas home and her hypochondriac mother 9 years ago. When she finally steps back into her childhood home, Katherine is immediately overwhelmed by the familiar. Every room seems to have a story. Every corner of the house holds another recollection. Katherine’s memories become so vivid, in fact, they appear to come alive before her eyes. Both humorous and heartbreaking, HOME explores parenting and childhood with unflinching honesty, questioning what it means to grow older, and whether we truly have the capacity to grow up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Me Bad</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/make-me-bad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2015 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/make-me-bad/</guid>
      <description>by special arrangement with The Benge Group
What happens when you fall in love with a serial killer? This gritty and sexy musical thriller follows the story of Daisy Harris, a young woman stuck in a small town with a dead-end job, an overbearing mother, and a troubled past. Desperate to escape but with nowhere to go, Daisy looks for anything to break the monotony of her meaningless life. She meets charming and cryptic Max, just as a string of unexplained murders rocks the town.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greta</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/greta/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/greta/</guid>
      <description>In the exciting next phase of its evolution, Kissing Frogs, one of BPP&amp;rsquo;s best-selling shows ever, returns for its second draft with some new songs and an all-new story. It all happened at the Stop Drop &amp;amp; Bowl. At least that&amp;rsquo;s how Greta&amp;rsquo;s beginning to feel about every major event in her life. After college, Greta puts her future on hold to help her grandmother run the family bowling alley, the very same one she grew up in.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>