<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Derek Gregor on Bloomington Playwrights Project</title>
    <link>http://newplays.org/musicians/derek-gregor/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Derek Gregor on Bloomington Playwrights Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2016 19:30:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://newplays.org/musicians/derek-gregor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Toast</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2015-2016/toast/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2016 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2015-2016/toast/</guid>
      <description>Based on the novella by Rex Rose. When Tania comes back home to New Orleans, she’s got one thing on her mind: finishing the beautiful tattoo across her back. But she finds her favorite nightclub in dire need of repair, her ex-boyfriend is slowly dying, and her rag tag group of bohemian friends is constantly changing. Carner and Gregor, authors of BPP audience favorite ISLAND SONG, return with an electric new musical about love, The Big Easy, and the difference between living a temporary life and a permanent one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Island Song</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/island-song/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/island-song/</guid>
      <description>The rush of the city keeps rhythmic time, and five young people traveling down uncertain paths are caught up in the pulse of life in New York. This cutting-edge new musical from the acclaimed songwriting duo, Carner and Gregor, examines the struggle of finding love, the struggle of finding success, and, above all, the struggle of finding yourself in a big city where everyone seems somehow interconnected. Produced in partnership with Indiana University Theatre &amp;amp; Drama, this innovative musical takes shape in a full production after its workshop on IU&amp;rsquo;s campus.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>