<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2014-2015 on Bloomington Playwrights Project</title>
    <link>http://newplays.org/series/2014-2015/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2014-2015 on Bloomington Playwrights Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 19:30:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://newplays.org/series/2014-2015/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Capables</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/the-capables/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/the-capables/</guid>
      <description>Anna Capable is a hoarder. The stacks of McDonald&amp;rsquo;s happy meal toys, beanie babies, and useless junk pile straight up to the ceiling, forcing her daughter, Jessy, to call a TV network in hopes of clearing the mess and curing her mother. But the TV network&amp;rsquo;s producer, David, is looking for more than just another cluttered home to get the ratings he needs. With his career on the line, he&amp;rsquo;s hungry to expose the Capables&amp;rsquo; dirty laundry &amp;ndash; whether it&amp;rsquo;s in their house, or their personal lives &amp;ndash; at all costs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ugly Lies the Bone</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/ugly-lies-the-bone/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/ugly-lies-the-bone/</guid>
      <description>Female soldier, Jess, returns from war severely burned only to find her Floridian hometown decaying with the end of the space shuttle era. She moves in with her sister and struggles through immense pain to define a new sense of &amp;ldquo;normal&amp;rdquo; when all she wants is her old life back. Using virtual reality therapy, Jess builds a dream world of cooling snow to calm her mind as she desperately tries to restore her relationships, home, and all that was lost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Me Bad</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/make-me-bad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2015 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/make-me-bad/</guid>
      <description>by special arrangement with The Benge Group
What happens when you fall in love with a serial killer? This gritty and sexy musical thriller follows the story of Daisy Harris, a young woman stuck in a small town with a dead-end job, an overbearing mother, and a troubled past. Desperate to escape but with nowhere to go, Daisy looks for anything to break the monotony of her meaningless life. She meets charming and cryptic Max, just as a string of unexplained murders rocks the town.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>She Kills Monsters</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/she-kills-monsters/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2014 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/she-kills-monsters/</guid>
      <description>Agnes never paid much attention to her teenage sister, Tilly, who took refuge in the role-playing world. But when a tragedy strikes and Tilly is lost forever, Agnes goes searching in the one place she can still be found: her late sister&amp;rsquo;s Dungeons &amp;amp; Dragons notebook. With the help of the game store clerk, Chuck, Agnes dives into the fantastical world of fairies, ogres, dragons, and even blood thirsty cheerleaders, in an action-packed comedy that searches for the warrior&amp;hellip; and the geek&amp;hellip; within us all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kalamazoo</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/kalamazoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2014 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/kalamazoo/</guid>
      <description>When Peg, a 70-something, Irish Catholic bird lover meets Irving, a 70-something Jewish, metal detector-toting East Coaster on an online dating site, it feels like love at first click. But after their crazy margarita-filled first date, complete with body shots and morning-after tattoos, Peg and Irving find that they still have a little aging to do if they want to forget their past and move forward into a future together.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>