<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2013-2014 on Bloomington Playwrights Project</title>
    <link>http://newplays.org/series/2013-2014/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2013-2014 on Bloomington Playwrights Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 19:30:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://newplays.org/series/2013-2014/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Greta</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/greta/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/greta/</guid>
      <description>In the exciting next phase of its evolution, Kissing Frogs, one of BPP&amp;rsquo;s best-selling shows ever, returns for its second draft with some new songs and an all-new story. It all happened at the Stop Drop &amp;amp; Bowl. At least that&amp;rsquo;s how Greta&amp;rsquo;s beginning to feel about every major event in her life. After college, Greta puts her future on hold to help her grandmother run the family bowling alley, the very same one she grew up in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mad Gravity</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/mad-gravity/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2014 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/mad-gravity/</guid>
      <description>Archie and Eudora have built a live studio audience in their living room. Being constantly observed helps them to lead an honest and honorable life. But things get awkward when some important visitors get a massive case of stage fright. Then, when it&amp;rsquo;s announced that an asteroid may be heading cataclysmically towards the Earth, all social order breaks down and the honest and honorable life takes a backseat to a frenzied, panicked mayhem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Island Song</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/island-song/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/island-song/</guid>
      <description>The rush of the city keeps rhythmic time, and five young people traveling down uncertain paths are caught up in the pulse of life in New York. This cutting-edge new musical from the acclaimed songwriting duo, Carner and Gregor, examines the struggle of finding love, the struggle of finding success, and, above all, the struggle of finding yourself in a big city where everyone seems somehow interconnected. Produced in partnership with Indiana University Theatre &amp;amp; Drama, this innovative musical takes shape in a full production after its workshop on IU&amp;rsquo;s campus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Banana Tree</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/the-banana-tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2013 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/the-banana-tree/</guid>
      <description>From the minds of The Simpsons stars, Dan Castellaneta (Homer Simpson) and Deb Lacusta (writer), comes a zany comedy about Angela, a convenience store clerk who dreams of being Las Vegas&amp;rsquo; first African American female magician. But after a series of hilarious run-ins and blunders, Angela finds herself in the middle of a robbery, a kidnapping, and at the mercy of a criminal mastermind that also happens to be a telepathic banana tree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sequence</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/sequence/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/sequence/</guid>
      <description>In this edge-of-your-seat science thriller, two intertwined stories teem with coincidence. In one, Time Magazine&amp;rsquo;s Luckiest Man Alive has correctly bet on the Super Bowl coin toss 19 years in a row. He is about to risk $880 million on the 20th until he&amp;rsquo;s confronted by a young woman who may be able to prove that mathematics is behind his &amp;ldquo;luck.&amp;rdquo; In the other, an extremely unlucky man improbably guesses wrong on all 150 multiple choice questions of his science exam, which he feels is a sign from a higher power.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>