<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Emily Goodson on Bloomington Playwrights Project</title>
    <link>http://newplays.org/playwrights/emily-goodson/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Emily Goodson on Bloomington Playwrights Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 19:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://newplays.org/playwrights/emily-goodson/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Spun: A Brother/Sister Rock Musical</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/spun/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/spun/</guid>
      <description>Back by popular demand, one of BPP’s most beloved musicals returns with 6 new songs and some new surprises in store. Don’t miss this encore performance as it prepares for an anticipated NYC run!
Following their father’s death, Molly and her estranged brother Jesse come home to pick up the pieces. But as they begin to recount their childhood together, two very different stories are revealed… and rock-n-roll tears through the past to uncover wounds that still must be healed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calling All Kates</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/calling-all-kates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2017 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/calling-all-kates/</guid>
      <description>Marc gets dumped by his fiancé, Kate McBride, right before their wedding and honeymoon around the world. He’s now single and left to travel the globe alone since his plane tickets are non-transferrable and non-refundable. In an act of desperation, Marc posts an ad online for the only companion who could legally join him&amp;hellip; someone with the exact same name as his ex-fiancé. Set loose in a bunch of different foreign countries, strangers Marc and Kate must get to know one another and learn to get along in the wake of Marc&amp;rsquo;s heartbreak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greta</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/greta/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/greta/</guid>
      <description>In the exciting next phase of its evolution, Kissing Frogs, one of BPP&amp;rsquo;s best-selling shows ever, returns for its second draft with some new songs and an all-new story. It all happened at the Stop Drop &amp;amp; Bowl. At least that&amp;rsquo;s how Greta&amp;rsquo;s beginning to feel about every major event in her life. After college, Greta puts her future on hold to help her grandmother run the family bowling alley, the very same one she grew up in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spun</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2012-2013/spun/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2013 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2012-2013/spun/</guid>
      <description>Following their father&amp;rsquo;s death, Molly and her estranged brother Jesse try to find a way to reconnect within the ruins of their childhood. But memories have a funny way of changing over time; and with two very different recollections blame, doubt, and rock &amp;lsquo;n&amp;rsquo; roll become weapons. The composer and lyricist of the hit Kissing Frogs, Jeremy Schonfeld returns to create this high-octane musical that explores the complexities of family and story-telling, weaving together the memories and unique perspectives of siblings with comedy, wit, and rock.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>