<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>drama on Bloomington Playwrights Project</title>
    <link>http://newplays.org/genres/drama/</link>
    <description>Recent content in drama on Bloomington Playwrights Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 19:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://newplays.org/genres/drama/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Out of Orbit</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/out-of-orbit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/out-of-orbit/</guid>
      <description>Sara, one of the world’s most brilliant planetary geologists, lives her life on Mars time — her days lasting longer and longer as she monitors mankind’s latest voyage to the Red Planet. But her daughter, Lis, continues to live her life as a teenager on Earth time, showing no interest in her mother’s world out in space—despite Sara’s best efforts. As both of their lives begin to spin out of control, they must grapple with the distance their two time zones create between them… even when they’re standing side by side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bull, the Moon and the Coronet of Stars</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2015-2016/the-bull-the-moon-and-the-coronet-of-stars/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2015-2016/the-bull-the-moon-and-the-coronet-of-stars/</guid>
      <description>Marion tries not to fall for Michael, her handsome (and very married) co-worker. But as Marion and Michael become entangled in each other, the museum where they work comes under a mysterious, mythological attack. A beast is roaming through the halls; a beast that threatens to destroy Marion’s capacity for love and to leave her wondering if she ever wants to find it again. The U.S. premiere of an award-winning new Australian play, THE BULL, THE MOON AND THE CORONET OF STARS is a magical, passionate, and charming love story of mythic proportions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Capables</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/the-capables/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/the-capables/</guid>
      <description>Anna Capable is a hoarder. The stacks of McDonald&amp;rsquo;s happy meal toys, beanie babies, and useless junk pile straight up to the ceiling, forcing her daughter, Jessy, to call a TV network in hopes of clearing the mess and curing her mother. But the TV network&amp;rsquo;s producer, David, is looking for more than just another cluttered home to get the ratings he needs. With his career on the line, he&amp;rsquo;s hungry to expose the Capables&amp;rsquo; dirty laundry &amp;ndash; whether it&amp;rsquo;s in their house, or their personal lives &amp;ndash; at all costs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ugly Lies the Bone</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/ugly-lies-the-bone/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/ugly-lies-the-bone/</guid>
      <description>Female soldier, Jess, returns from war severely burned only to find her Floridian hometown decaying with the end of the space shuttle era. She moves in with her sister and struggles through immense pain to define a new sense of &amp;ldquo;normal&amp;rdquo; when all she wants is her old life back. Using virtual reality therapy, Jess builds a dream world of cooling snow to calm her mind as she desperately tries to restore her relationships, home, and all that was lost.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>