<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2012-2013 on Bloomington Playwrights Project</title>
    <link>http://newplays.org/series/2012-2013/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2012-2013 on Bloomington Playwrights Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 May 2013 19:30:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://newplays.org/series/2012-2013/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Spun</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2012-2013/spun/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2013 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2012-2013/spun/</guid>
      <description>Following their father&amp;rsquo;s death, Molly and her estranged brother Jesse try to find a way to reconnect within the ruins of their childhood. But memories have a funny way of changing over time; and with two very different recollections blame, doubt, and rock &amp;lsquo;n&amp;rsquo; roll become weapons. The composer and lyricist of the hit Kissing Frogs, Jeremy Schonfeld returns to create this high-octane musical that explores the complexities of family and story-telling, weaving together the memories and unique perspectives of siblings with comedy, wit, and rock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ampersand</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2012-2013/ampersand/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2013 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2012-2013/ampersand/</guid>
      <description>Things aren&amp;rsquo;t working out for Kate and Marlowe. He&amp;rsquo;s an unemployed whiner, and despite her best efforts to stick with him, Kate just couldn&amp;rsquo;t help cloning him. Twice. When one of the clones slips into Marlowe&amp;rsquo;s life, and Kate discovers that she might not actually be the original Kate, things get scarier and funnier at the same time. Just what is marriage? And how far will we go to change each other—and ourselves—to stay together?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Truman Show</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2012-2013/the-truman-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2012-2013/the-truman-show/</guid>
      <description>Based on the original film by Andrew Niccol
Based on the beloved 1998 film, this musical follows Truman, an ordinary man unaware he&amp;rsquo;s being watched by millions from all over the world. He lives in a large studio with hidden cameras everywhere. All his friends and townspeople are actors playing their roles in the most popular TV-series in the world: &amp;ldquo;The Truman Show&amp;rdquo;. When an actress falls in love with him, she breaks onto the set to tell him the truth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lemonade</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2012-2013/lemonade/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2012 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2012-2013/lemonade/</guid>
      <description>Ever hear the one about the unsuccessful comedian and his garbage sculpting wife? They strive for the American dream while struggling to pay their bills, escape eviction and cope with friends who increasingly seem like strangers. Life, they tell their kids, is sort of like Dad&amp;rsquo;s monologues: no matter how fearlessly you struggle you&amp;rsquo;re only as good as your punch line.
Lemonade was chosen as the best out of 450 submissions from around the world as part of its Woodward/Newman Drama Competition, named after two of the greatest actors of our time, Joanne Woodward &amp;amp; Paul Newman and sponsored by Newman&amp;rsquo;s Own Foundation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rx</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2012-2013/rx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2012-2013/rx/</guid>
      <description>Meena Pierotti&amp;rsquo;s job is making her unhappy. Luckily, there&amp;rsquo;s a pill for that. Well, not yet. But Meena has joined the clinical trial for a new drug targeting workplace depression. The trial gets messy, however, when her doctor falls in love with her, and he chooses to enroll himself in a drug trial targeting heartbreak.
The BPP&amp;rsquo;s Off-Broadway/On-9th series seeks to take a play recently seen at a small theatre in NYC and help it to have a future life across the country by producing it here at the BPP at 9th Street.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>