<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chad Rabinovitz on Bloomington Playwrights Project</title>
    <link>http://newplays.org/directors/chad-rabinovitz/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Chad Rabinovitz on Bloomington Playwrights Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 19:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://newplays.org/directors/chad-rabinovitz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Jedi Handbook</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2018-2019/the-jedi-handbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2018-2019/the-jedi-handbook/</guid>
      <description>A not so long time ago, in a theater not so far away, came a film that rocked the galaxy – changing both cinema and schoolyards forever…
The Jedi Handbook is a coming of age story about a young boy who survives growing older with help from The Force. Experiencing the Star Wars franchise anew, through the eyes and imagination of a kid, The Jedi Handbook takes us on a nostalgic journey back to an era we can all relate to – our childhood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glitches in Reality</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2018-2019/glitches-in-reality/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2018-2019/glitches-in-reality/</guid>
      <description>From the mind of renowned Australian magician, Simon Coronel, comes an evening filled with astonishing and impossible events. Glitches in Reality uses close-up trickery and mind-blowing sleight of hand to take the audience on a journey through the truth behind magic and illusion; a truth that is far more amazing than even the illusions themselves.
Winner of over a dozen international awards including multiple from the prestigious World Championships of Magic, Simon is a regular performer at the Magic Castle and is a university lecturer on perception and illusion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spun: A Brother/Sister Rock Musical</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/spun/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/spun/</guid>
      <description>Back by popular demand, one of BPP’s most beloved musicals returns with 6 new songs and some new surprises in store. Don’t miss this encore performance as it prepares for an anticipated NYC run!
Following their father’s death, Molly and her estranged brother Jesse come home to pick up the pieces. But as they begin to recount their childhood together, two very different stories are revealed… and rock-n-roll tears through the past to uncover wounds that still must be healed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calling All Kates</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/calling-all-kates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2017 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/calling-all-kates/</guid>
      <description>Marc gets dumped by his fiancé, Kate McBride, right before their wedding and honeymoon around the world. He’s now single and left to travel the globe alone since his plane tickets are non-transferrable and non-refundable. In an act of desperation, Marc posts an ad online for the only companion who could legally join him&amp;hellip; someone with the exact same name as his ex-fiancé. Set loose in a bunch of different foreign countries, strangers Marc and Kate must get to know one another and learn to get along in the wake of Marc&amp;rsquo;s heartbreak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2016-2017/home/</guid>
      <description>Katherine escaped from her small Texas home and her hypochondriac mother 9 years ago. When she finally steps back into her childhood home, Katherine is immediately overwhelmed by the familiar. Every room seems to have a story. Every corner of the house holds another recollection. Katherine’s memories become so vivid, in fact, they appear to come alive before her eyes. Both humorous and heartbreaking, HOME explores parenting and childhood with unflinching honesty, questioning what it means to grow older, and whether we truly have the capacity to grow up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everything in its Place</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2015-2016/everything-in-its-place/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2016 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2015-2016/everything-in-its-place/</guid>
      <description>You may know him from his time hosting Nickelodeon&amp;rsquo;s Double Dare and Food Network&amp;rsquo;s Unwrapped, or as the Producer of hits like Dinner:Impossible and Restaurant:Impossible, but now you get the chance to meet the real Marc Summers &amp;ndash; a man who&amp;rsquo;s led a fascinating life of fame and frustration. Everything in its Place is a guided tour through Marc&amp;rsquo;s life, from an early obsession with magic to his notable television career and his struggles with OCD.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bull, the Moon and the Coronet of Stars</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2015-2016/the-bull-the-moon-and-the-coronet-of-stars/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2015-2016/the-bull-the-moon-and-the-coronet-of-stars/</guid>
      <description>Marion tries not to fall for Michael, her handsome (and very married) co-worker. But as Marion and Michael become entangled in each other, the museum where they work comes under a mysterious, mythological attack. A beast is roaming through the halls; a beast that threatens to destroy Marion’s capacity for love and to leave her wondering if she ever wants to find it again. The U.S. premiere of an award-winning new Australian play, THE BULL, THE MOON AND THE CORONET OF STARS is a magical, passionate, and charming love story of mythic proportions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Me Bad</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/make-me-bad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2015 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/make-me-bad/</guid>
      <description>by special arrangement with The Benge Group
What happens when you fall in love with a serial killer? This gritty and sexy musical thriller follows the story of Daisy Harris, a young woman stuck in a small town with a dead-end job, an overbearing mother, and a troubled past. Desperate to escape but with nowhere to go, Daisy looks for anything to break the monotony of her meaningless life. She meets charming and cryptic Max, just as a string of unexplained murders rocks the town.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kalamazoo</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/kalamazoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2014 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/kalamazoo/</guid>
      <description>When Peg, a 70-something, Irish Catholic bird lover meets Irving, a 70-something Jewish, metal detector-toting East Coaster on an online dating site, it feels like love at first click. But after their crazy margarita-filled first date, complete with body shots and morning-after tattoos, Peg and Irving find that they still have a little aging to do if they want to forget their past and move forward into a future together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Banana Tree</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/the-banana-tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2013 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/the-banana-tree/</guid>
      <description>From the minds of The Simpsons stars, Dan Castellaneta (Homer Simpson) and Deb Lacusta (writer), comes a zany comedy about Angela, a convenience store clerk who dreams of being Las Vegas&amp;rsquo; first African American female magician. But after a series of hilarious run-ins and blunders, Angela finds herself in the middle of a robbery, a kidnapping, and at the mercy of a criminal mastermind that also happens to be a telepathic banana tree.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>