<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ivy Tech-BPP Youth Education on Bloomington Playwrights Project</title>
    <link>http://newplays.org/education/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ivy Tech-BPP Youth Education on Bloomington Playwrights Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2011 00:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://newplays.org/education/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>MiniPlay Playwriting Contest</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/education/miniplay-playwriting-contest/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2016 11:54:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/education/miniplay-playwriting-contest/</guid>
      <description>The highly successful and long-running MiniPlay Contest invites students in 1st-8th grades to participate and write a short play on the topic of EXPLORERS. 1st, 2nd, and 3rd place MiniPlay winners will receive public recognition and a staged reading (April 5, 2020) of their winning play by local actors at a special MiniPlay Premiere Party with Ice Cream and Pizza! Plus NEW THIS YEAR, Grand Prize winners in each category will also receive a $50 cash prize!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>After School EdVentures</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/education/after-school-edventures/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2016 11:54:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/education/after-school-edventures/</guid>
      <description>The BPP offers drama clubs for elementary students through the After School EdVentures program.
Where? These clubs take place at Fairview, Templeton, Arlington Heights, Grandview, Summit, and Highland Park elementary schools.
What? When? Students in drama club learn and practice using the actors&amp;rsquo; tools of body, voice and imagination and develop skills to work creatively and collaboratively through improvisation and creative dramatics. K-2 students adapt a story, and older students collaborate on short skits for performance at the final class.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musical Theater Camp</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/education/musical-theater-camp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2016 11:54:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/education/musical-theater-camp/</guid>
      <description>Ages 9 - 16 July 8 - July 26, 2019 Performances July 26 and 27 at 7pm Monday - Friday; 9am - 4pm, $395 Register today! Email education@newplays.org for more info.  Campers will work with BPP professionals to write and produce an exciting new musical starring them! Students will start by learning about - and singing songs from - popular Broadway musicals. They&amp;rsquo;ll train as actors, singers, dancers, playwrights, and designers as they learn every element that goes into putting on a show.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laugh Factory</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/education/laugh-factory/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2016 11:53:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/education/laugh-factory/</guid>
      <description>Ages 9 - 13 June 24 - July 5, 2019 Performances July 5 and 6 at 7pm 9am - 4pm $325 Register today! Email education@newplays.org for more info.  Do you have a funny kid at the dinner table? Do they practice their jokes for you hours on end or stay up late to watch Saturday Night Live? Then send them over to BPP’s Laugh Factory where they’ll learn to perfect their comedic acting, joke writing, and improv abilities!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DramatiKIDS</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/education/dramatikids/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2016 11:53:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/education/dramatikids/</guid>
      <description>Ages 8 - 12 $295 June 10 - June 21, 2019 performances June 21 and 22 at 7pm Monday - Friday; 9am - 4pm Register today! Email education@newplays.org for more info.   A virtual playground for young imaginations, DramatiKIDS is the perfect opportunity for young actors and writers to explore their creativity, learning skills in both acting and playwriting, culminating in an opportunity to star in a play they write themselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Broadway Kids</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/education/broadway-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2016 11:53:09 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/education/broadway-kids/</guid>
      <description>Ages 5-8 Session 1: May 27 - May 31, 2019 - $200 (Please note: Day 1 is Memorial Day, but attendance is optional) performance on May 31 at 7PM Session 2: June 3 - June 7, 2019 - $200 Register for both sessions for $350 Monday - Friday; 9am - 4pm Register today! Email education@newplays.org for more info.  Participants will explore the world of theatre through music, movement, visual arts, and performance.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>