<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2015-2016 Season on Bloomington Playwrights Project</title>
    <link>http://newplays.org/show/2015-2016/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2015-2016 Season on Bloomington Playwrights Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 08:34:12 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://newplays.org/show/2015-2016/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>You Remind Me of You</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2015-2016/you-remind-me-of-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2015-2016/you-remind-me-of-you/</guid>
      <description>Adele has abandoned her law school plans and her social life to take care of her addled father – a man who has trouble remembering who she is. A chance encounter with a musician named Vincent might just be the best thing to ever happen to her. The catch: Vincent has a rare neurological condition – he has face blindness. This season’s Woodward/Newman Drama Award winning play explores what it’s like to love without recognition and how two people might just keep each other from disappearing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everything in its Place</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2015-2016/everything-in-its-place/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2016 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2015-2016/everything-in-its-place/</guid>
      <description>You may know him from his time hosting Nickelodeon&amp;rsquo;s Double Dare and Food Network&amp;rsquo;s Unwrapped, or as the Producer of hits like Dinner:Impossible and Restaurant:Impossible, but now you get the chance to meet the real Marc Summers &amp;ndash; a man who&amp;rsquo;s led a fascinating life of fame and frustration. Everything in its Place is a guided tour through Marc&amp;rsquo;s life, from an early obsession with magic to his notable television career and his struggles with OCD.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toast</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2015-2016/toast/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2016 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2015-2016/toast/</guid>
      <description>Based on the novella by Rex Rose. When Tania comes back home to New Orleans, she’s got one thing on her mind: finishing the beautiful tattoo across her back. But she finds her favorite nightclub in dire need of repair, her ex-boyfriend is slowly dying, and her rag tag group of bohemian friends is constantly changing. Carner and Gregor, authors of BPP audience favorite ISLAND SONG, return with an electric new musical about love, The Big Easy, and the difference between living a temporary life and a permanent one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Billy Witch</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2015-2016/billy-witch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2015 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2015-2016/billy-witch/</guid>
      <description>Oliver is hoping that summer camp will change him. Somewhere in the bizarre mixture of secrets and s’mores; sexual exploration and swimming; ghosts, girls and god’s eyes; somewhere in all that mess&amp;hellip;Oliver just might grow up. Travel back to a time when we were all innocent in this riotously funny and disarmingly tender Reva Shiner Comedy Award winning play about the awkward (and often hysterical) transformation from youth to adolescence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bull, the Moon and the Coronet of Stars</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2015-2016/the-bull-the-moon-and-the-coronet-of-stars/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2015-2016/the-bull-the-moon-and-the-coronet-of-stars/</guid>
      <description>Marion tries not to fall for Michael, her handsome (and very married) co-worker. But as Marion and Michael become entangled in each other, the museum where they work comes under a mysterious, mythological attack. A beast is roaming through the halls; a beast that threatens to destroy Marion’s capacity for love and to leave her wondering if she ever wants to find it again. The U.S. premiere of an award-winning new Australian play, THE BULL, THE MOON AND THE CORONET OF STARS is a magical, passionate, and charming love story of mythic proportions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>