<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Woodward/Newman Drama Award Winner on Bloomington Playwrights Project</title>
    <link>http://newplays.org/awards/woodward-newman-drama-award-winner/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Woodward/Newman Drama Award Winner on Bloomington Playwrights Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 19:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://newplays.org/awards/woodward-newman-drama-award-winner/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Out of Orbit</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/out-of-orbit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2017-2018/out-of-orbit/</guid>
      <description>Sara, one of the world’s most brilliant planetary geologists, lives her life on Mars time — her days lasting longer and longer as she monitors mankind’s latest voyage to the Red Planet. But her daughter, Lis, continues to live her life as a teenager on Earth time, showing no interest in her mother’s world out in space—despite Sara’s best efforts. As both of their lives begin to spin out of control, they must grapple with the distance their two time zones create between them… even when they’re standing side by side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ugly Lies the Bone</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/ugly-lies-the-bone/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2014-2015/ugly-lies-the-bone/</guid>
      <description>Female soldier, Jess, returns from war severely burned only to find her Floridian hometown decaying with the end of the space shuttle era. She moves in with her sister and struggles through immense pain to define a new sense of &amp;ldquo;normal&amp;rdquo; when all she wants is her old life back. Using virtual reality therapy, Jess builds a dream world of cooling snow to calm her mind as she desperately tries to restore her relationships, home, and all that was lost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sequence</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/sequence/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2013-2014/sequence/</guid>
      <description>In this edge-of-your-seat science thriller, two intertwined stories teem with coincidence. In one, Time Magazine&amp;rsquo;s Luckiest Man Alive has correctly bet on the Super Bowl coin toss 19 years in a row. He is about to risk $880 million on the 20th until he&amp;rsquo;s confronted by a young woman who may be able to prove that mathematics is behind his &amp;ldquo;luck.&amp;rdquo; In the other, an extremely unlucky man improbably guesses wrong on all 150 multiple choice questions of his science exam, which he feels is a sign from a higher power.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lemonade</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2012-2013/lemonade/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2012 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2012-2013/lemonade/</guid>
      <description>Ever hear the one about the unsuccessful comedian and his garbage sculpting wife? They strive for the American dream while struggling to pay their bills, escape eviction and cope with friends who increasingly seem like strangers. Life, they tell their kids, is sort of like Dad&amp;rsquo;s monologues: no matter how fearlessly you struggle you&amp;rsquo;re only as good as your punch line.
Lemonade was chosen as the best out of 450 submissions from around the world as part of its Woodward/Newman Drama Competition, named after two of the greatest actors of our time, Joanne Woodward &amp;amp; Paul Newman and sponsored by Newman&amp;rsquo;s Own Foundation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>