<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2018-2019s on Bloomington Playwrights Project</title>
    <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2018-2019s on Bloomington Playwrights Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 18:30:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>BPP&#39;s 40th Birthday Celebration</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/vintage-songs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 18:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/vintage-songs/</guid>
      <description>This June 6th, we are throwing ourselves a 40th Birthday Celebration! Start the night out at 6:30 with donated food, wine, and beer! Then move into the theatre for the announcement of our 2019-2020 Season and a staged read of the 2014 SMASH HIT Kalamazoo. Join the original cast and relive the wonderful story of BPP&amp;rsquo;s best selling show of all time. Then stick around for the announcement of the 2019-20 Season (our 40th!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ike &amp; Julie Arnove PlayOffs</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/ike-and-julie-arnove-playoffs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/ike-and-julie-arnove-playoffs/</guid>
      <description>Batter up for the Ike &amp;amp; Julie Arnove PlayOffs! It&amp;rsquo;s almost that time of year again when we separate the contenders from the pretenders, the pros from the joes, the heroes from the zeros. Yes, that’s right - the baseball playoffs are just around the corner. In celebration, the BPP is presenting its most electrifying, action-packed, and anticipated fundraising event of the year, the Ike &amp;amp; Julie Arnove PlayOffs!
Just what are The PlayOffs, you ask?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Your Marc</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/on-your-marc-screening/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2018-2019/on-your-marc-screening/</guid>
      <description>Do you remember back in 2016 when beloved TV icon, Marc Summers, premiered his one-man show Everything in Its Place: The Life and Slimes of Marc Summers at BPP? We sure do. Well, while that was going on, a documentary crew was filming.
Fast forward 2 years&amp;hellip; Surprise! Marc is joining us again this fall for a sneak preview screening of the completed film! On Your Marc intimately captures his life, career, and legacy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>