<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2019-2020 on Bloomington Playwrights Project</title>
    <link>http://newplays.org/series/2019-2020/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2019-2020 on Bloomington Playwrights Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 18:30:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://newplays.org/series/2019-2020/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>BPP&#39;s 41st Birthday Celebration</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2019-2020/bpps-birthday-bash/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 18:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2019-2020/bpps-birthday-bash/</guid>
      <description>After how much fun we had last year, BPP is throwing itself another Birthday Celebration in 2020! Start the night out at 6:30 with donated food, wine, and beer! Then move into the theatre for the announcement of our 2020-2021 Season and a staged reading of the 2011 SMASH HIT Still the River Runs starring the original cast (Gabe Gloden &amp;amp; Daniel J. Petrie). Then stick around for the announcement of the 2020-21 Season (our 41st!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Burdens</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/the-burdens/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/the-burdens/</guid>
      <description>Siblings Mordy and Jane communicate like proper millennials: primarily through text message and loaded with sarcasm. When their loving mother’s life becomes emotionally and financially taxed by their absolutely awful and 100-year-old grandfather, Zad-Zad, they draw together an elaborate plot to…relieve their mother’s burden. Told almost entirely via text messages, The Burdens is a dark, family comedy about how technology helps keep us close, while still enabling us to keep our distance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Absentee</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/the-absentee/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/the-absentee/</guid>
      <description>Far out in the Milky Way, “Beacons” serve as lighthouses for warping spaceships around the galaxy. When a U.S. Space Forces ship explodes near Beacon 44.AR.90, its Operator finds herself alone in deep space with only her ship’s AI for companionship. That is, until a persistent canvasser calls, desperate to convince her to vote absentee in the 2088 election.
Box office opens at 6:30pm, house opens at 7pm, shows begin at 7:30pm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>40 Days of Dinner</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2019-2020/30-days-of-dinners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2019-2020/30-days-of-dinners/</guid>
      <description>You are invited to BPP&amp;rsquo;s 40 Days of Dinner. It happens over the entire month of February and into March instead of one single day, so you can find the day that works best for you! Tired of seeing the same 100 people at stuffy ballroom gatherings? We have close knit dinners and parties at the homes of some of the world&amp;rsquo;s greatest hosts. There is something for everyone.
Masquerades, Detective Mysteries, Viewing parties, Game Nights, Tapas dinners, Wine tastings and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Enlightenment of Percival Von Schmootz</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/percival-von-schmootz/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/percival-von-schmootz/</guid>
      <description>Fed up with a world filled with plagues, pestilence, and poor personal hygiene, a ridiculously optimistic young man sets out on a quest to end the Dark Ages. As he attempts to bring the light of hope to the world, Percival Von Schmootz meets with hilariously disastrous results at every turn. Yet in this outrageous, Monty Python-esque musical comedy, it is only when things look the darkest that Percival is able to discover what true enlightenment means, as he finds hope (and humor) in impossibly bleak circumstances.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lost Letters</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/lost-letters/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/lost-letters/</guid>
      <description>Newly married, newly moved, and with a newborn on the way, Adam is scrambling to get everything ready for the arrival of his daughter – all the while questioning the choices that brought him to this moment. While clearing out boxes from his soon-to-be nursery, he finds a trove of handwritten letters from his past. The letters come to life and force Adam to (finally) reply, make peace with the present, and embrace his new reality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ike &amp; Julie Arnove PlayOffs</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2019-2020/ike-and-julie-arnove-playoffs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 19:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2019-2020/ike-and-julie-arnove-playoffs/</guid>
      <description>Batter up for the Ike &amp;amp; Julie Arnove PlayOffs! It&amp;rsquo;s almost that time of year again when we separate the contenders from the pretenders, the pros from the joes, the heroes from the zeros. Yes, that’s right - the baseball playoffs are just around the corner. In celebration, the BPP is presenting its most electrifying, action-packed, and anticipated fundraising event of the year, the Ike &amp;amp; Julie Arnove PlayOffs!
Just what are The PlayOffs, you ask?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simon Coronel&#39;s Magic Smackdown</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2019-2020/simon-coronels-magic-smackdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2019 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2019-2020/simon-coronels-magic-smackdown/</guid>
      <description>Simon Coronel’s Magic Smackdown combines the amazing magic of Penn &amp;amp; Teller’s Fool Us, the humor and fun of Whose Line Is It Anyway, and the excitement of live voting you find on American Idol. This wholly original evening of entertainment stars award-winning stage and television magicians (and regulars of the Magic Castle) competing for both your attention and your affection. It’s an exhilarating and interactive magic show that will keep you laughing and amazed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mind Tricks with Max Major</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/event/2019-2020/mind-tricks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/event/2019-2020/mind-tricks/</guid>
      <description>World-renowned mentalist, Max Major, has given over 2,000 live performances and 100 television appearances. But after he baffled our minds at BPP in 2017 with his latest show, Max took a sudden and unexpected break from performing to focus on his most difficult trick yet: recovering from Lyme disease. Two years later, he’s traveling back to BPP to make his triumphant return to the stage and picking up where he left off, with a new outlook on life and incredible new feats of mind-reading and magic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rap Guide to Consciousness</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/rap-guide-to-conciousnes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/rap-guide-to-conciousnes/</guid>
      <description>PLEASE BE AWARE: Rap Guide to Consciousness and Rap Guide to Culture are SOLD SEPERATLY.
“Peer reviewed rapper” Baba Brinkman takes a deep dive into the neuroscience of human experience, from sensations to hallucinations. “Mind-blowingly, awe-inspiringly good”. (Broadway Baby) Baba’s brain consists of tens of billions of neurons, none of which has any idea that he exists. And yet, somehow, those cells come together to produce a steady stream of ill rhymes, laughs, and revelations about the mind we live in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rap Guide to Culture</title>
      <link>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/rap-guide-to-culture/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2019 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newplays.org/show/2019-2020/rap-guide-to-culture/</guid>
      <description>PLEASE BE AWARE: Rap Guide to Consciousness and Rap Guide to Culture are SOLD SEPERATLY.
Music, poetry, art, science, politics, and relationships are all strange behaviors found in a species of (mostly) hairless primates. How do norms and social systems evolve, and who benefits? The whole planet hangs in the balance as cultures and sub-cultures compete for survival and the reach to become viral. Equal parts rap concert, TED Talk, and stand-up gig, Rap Guide to Culture surprises, delights, and ultimately heals, bringing a wealth of knowledge and razor-sharp observational wit to some of today’s stickiest topics.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>